Like I don't know this guy's coming at me look at what's going on
Come to the night, the car's laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
door
Okay, there's a work down. Hold on. I'm sorry. Hello
You know you hear me now. Okay, I think it works now. Yay. Okay. And what's up guys?
It's a little bit of a quiet night
It's been there, you know, oh good. Yeah, perfect. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I can only only see one of my
I had things right now, a good moment right there.
Oh, I'm sure it will turn up.
I've been doing some art, you know, some graphic art.
Okay, good guys.
Yeah, there was just, you know, last night, twice in a row,
I think it was Aldi and then it was the other guy in the panel.
I don't remember his name exactly, but.
Yeah, oh, yeah, you remember that guy that was like, you know, he's he's like
He's what he's white, but he sounds black. And like and not to be racist about I mean, it's like he just like sounds
You know, he's like, I'm
But if anyone knows that was he was like saying like just really disgusting things about like, you know, I
Don't know and then in so was all these like I don't understand why they have to say
I had to leave a lot of streams last night, luckily it was not too crowded.
Getting a lot of stuff done for the channel, like I started some, you know, they can have
Stuff for t-shirts. I have some taco stuff. I need to make more talk. There's tacos jokes, but they're not fish tacos
Yeah, but I will marshy was live and
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, that guy with the guy's name was led or something like that
It's light so I'm not lights on who's you know that guy is
Do not care
I think it's a very passive aggressive die from him. Anyway, I've decided that,
actually, there was this quote every day. It's like, there's this quote, it says,
let them, you know, he's forced to live by it, let them. It's like, people are gonna do this and
this and this and this and this and say this and this and this and this, just let them.
Yeah, good look at other system, you know, hey
There you go, oh, gosh, hopefully I can find my other headphone
Here oh the mess
Hopefully it will turn up
No place is open now. Did I post the link? Okay, I'll pin the link too
Hey, what's going on man? Hello. Yeah, I get a big party last night, huh?
So I have a big party. I did not quite
You know you weren't partying all night
Yeah, it was like it was a dead class night. It was like
At one point like it was a 10 minutes and no one had said anything in the chat and then it was just like people on the panel talking about your nonsense and so I just like hold on I just uh
I need to show it early. Hold on. There we go.
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning.
Easy. What up man?
Oh shit. I didn't recognize you. Usually I got to pray to God in the morning.
Well you don't have to pray right now man.
I hear you man. I could be a dick too sometimes but um my question is I was junk drunk last night
So I ain't come up here while I'm right
Is you um where you're asking me?
Um, probably was it you you were in the film with led last night or no? No, no, no, no, no, no
I think clever whoever was on talking to him. I don't know if it was kz or something. There is like super
They're just talking about like using really graphic language about you know, you know
There's there's a talking like a really disgusting stuff and they're getting really weird way and so I just like end this show
So it was I think I was still here. I think I came early early early early. I was drunk drunk
As I thought I don't know if you heard that part of it
But I don't remember who it is now because I just leaked the stream. I wasn't here, right? I wasn't up there
I don't believe so. It was the uh, I'll talk about the guy. I'm LED
Oh
And yes, that's one of uh, yeah, it's one of he's boys
My boy correct yourself. He's not my boy
Like a white guy he sounds black he's white. I mean, it's like he's this big is he white
He's white. Oh, he's perfect. I'm sorry. Yeah, all this Puerto Rico sound like black guys. I'm sorry
You do? No, that's very racist. No, no
Yeah, I don't know. I always get fooled
But yeah, I mean it was like I don't need to hear about
Graphic graphic violent, you know, I don't I don't remember they're talking about it
I'm surprised. I was like, yo, I wake up and psyche's not lobby be there is
Sweeping oh, I'm not doing that. Sweeping not yet
I think beat it was having fun. You can't can't pay attention to the chat got you in conversation. No, she asked me a question. That's all
Yeah
Oh, that's they turns dude. Okay. Yeah. Oh, they turn it was they turn. Oh
Yeah, and it's like I don't care. I mean, it's like not to be like, you know
I don't there's a certain guests that are just like rubbing me the wrong way at this time, you know, it's like
They think they coming from that other platform and to bring it they bring it into your platform and not knowing that it's completely different platform
I have been I have been I've been kicking people off panel. I've been like, you know, just like
Giving them sometimes the chance to like say something. Hey, you kicked me from accidentally reading the chat
I know it's okay
That's what I say is good because you're protecting your page
Even if it comes to me or anybody you really like you're protecting your page and your page is above anybody else
So it'll matter. Yeah, and then like last night's sick was like, oh, yeah, we're striking your pay
I don't know. He was just like saying this is weird stuff
He's like we're already did it like well and like I don't know like I guess I guess I don't know what he's trying to
you know, say whatever. But I'm just like, you know, I've been through all the, I've been through
all the gas, lady, all the, all the, all the
subliminal stuff, all the, you know, you know, just like the passive aggressiveness people do.
I've been through all the games and it's like, and so I see them and it's like, so I'm not like,
I don't know, I'm just like, they don't really work on me. So, but it's like, but, so people will just have to, you know,
We're all like, oh, yeah, no, no, I know I'm a little stuck in the subject of change
I'm not I was online with one of my friends well group of friends actually last night
That's what I was trying to say, but you ready you ready a little go
I was on I was online with my friend cast and Hector old-school guy. So my pain was in shit. Oh, you know Hector
You don't know Hector Hector. You don't know I know Hector. How's Hector doing man? What's his name Hector from the Bronx?
And what what we call him?
What do you mean Hector Hector G? No, no, no, no
Yeah, you call him turtleneck. Oh
Yeah, you got a turtleneck. That's if you know what that means. Yeah, I know what that means
Funny guy
Another another panel we was all chilling those old-school vibes and I've been on panel with those guys in a minute
So it was just straight fun. Then I do that OD drug
Okay, so um, yeah
I mean
You know, um, you know, we have Kate the turtle. That's all I know about turtles really
Trust like when your French girls. Oh, yeah, guys. I have like a I just started to do electronic drawings, too
Also, let me see if I find this funny picture. I'm psyche is me him
Me here made all three of us we was on a e-bike in in in summer, and we was acting like ET go home. Oh
Shit
Did you draw Marcy Fox shit? Oh
I've been doing a lot of joints too. Yeah, no, I haven't draw hookers. I don't gotta still say a still frame of her yet
It'll be hard for you guys to capture beauty. I've been doing all right. I've been doing all right
Oh
What up, what up, what up?
What up everybody
Good man chilling
This came up to burn the blunt. I see what up a child for a little while
I need one right now
I'm on my way to pick something up though in a few
to two nice joints straight weed please stop calling you
what about you me did you draw you me
um I will also I also I'm gonna do uh you know stories and uh AI songs with people to see you
so I mean as people come up so
Um, you know, there's just depends on where I feel it. I mean, it's like, you know, I will do them once in a while
They will be
Channeled to I will put some channel information
So they'll be pretty cool. Okay. Yeah, I have a lot of new ideas to with this show. I have a lot of
Oh, yeah, they go to summers too last night. Thank you marshy
Yeah, so if you know you guys familiar with flying monkeys flying monkeys are a term for
You know in the Wizard of Oz there's these flying monkeys, right?
They work for the wicked witch and they go basically to go, you know, this spot goes by on Dorothy cool. Knapp todo
But uh, yeah, so who's who's saying that they're there's one of their favorite season of Wizard of Oz when the witches like flying in the sky
And she right surrender Dorothy. I mean it's like that is just
Psychonics on the bike. Yeah, well, she's on no shit. That's when she's like she's on the broom. Actually, it's when she's an odds
You're right. Oh, yeah. Yeah, the emerald city. That is a good scene. Actually. Yeah. Yeah
I surrender Dorothy
Dorothy Dorothy
So, yeah, I'm a
Yeah, that was actually the Wizard of Oz is so so iconic. It's still one of those movies that
resonate
With people
Feeling of meeting these certain like special like people along this journey and then it's like all of a sudden
I was kind of like a dream. I don't know
It's like a quest movie people love a quest good quest movie
Yeah, well that or Lord of the Rings or some shit like that
Yeah, let me in Lord of the Rings. That's like Lord of the Rings and things like that go way too complicated for me
I came after right lower the rings came after a before. Oh, yeah, I came after lower the rings are pretty recent
Wizard of Oz came out in what 18? Oh, yeah, it was all came our way before well
If you think about it, there's the old there's two old-school versions of it. So which one came out first first
The book with the book is that 1800s. Yeah 1870s or something. Oh Frank bomb
He was a Theosophist, which is like, you know, Helena Blavatsky's little group.
I was hoping he would be alive to see the movie made, but I think he died right before
it was made a couple years before.
Yep.
And you don't think he saw it?
That would have been sick.
And somebody blocked Doug D. He wrote Psyche's something.
Not pretty cool.
And we do you see it's like you play wow the D. Really? I
Really have not been paying too much attention to the time. I mean I think I will if I think things are brought to my attention
but it's like I am like
I'm like worrying a bunch of stuff today to like
Give my house clean. I'm worrying a bunch of stuff. What do you say chemo? What's a chemo? Hey, what?
Other word is the other word closer to it. Don't even say it. Don't say it. Don't say cuz I don't
I'll say it's a word that's about to be banned in my chat
It's one of those I'm not falling for chat no more. I'm not falling for chat. I'm gonna say read the chat
yeah you know but mods I do have a yeah man Erickson Marcy Fox you know you
know you know that's kind of it's a slander stuff and so can delete those
kind of comments I don't like who tried dimbo dimbo dingle I think
Don't know
And it's a gag and guys you don't have to you know, I don't expect you guys to like you don't have to like you know
Modest oh, hey, Christine. How are you?
How are you?
Christine, you have to hear the song, you have to hear the song yet, I mean it's so funny.
Wait, I think I heard it last night, I think that was the last thing I heard before I left.
Yeah, you heard the song. Yeah, because Christine's name is in it, like I'm gonna write another one
with Gotti's name in it, easy. I mean, I'm gonna put in the input, you accidentally, uh...
Okay, yeah, you're gonna have to use a different name for Gotti and me because it's hard to bring
up our names and stuff like that. I hope it's flattering.
Oh, I mean it was like I mean I'll just I mean I'm gonna I put in just some some suggestions with the AI though
They're very vague suggestions, and they they basically the gate that it just it just
Takes over itself. Okay, so yeah, so we can now hide like put this person like this Dave
Yeah, this person will be hidden. Okay, so that is
No, you don't see that kind of
Slanderous, okay. Can you hide that person, please? You know Doug is gone. It's fine. He's now he's gone too far
All right
That's why I said just read. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna say it. I'm not falling for it no more
I know it's just ridiculous and so bye, I'll never talk to you again and you will be banished to
Purgatory basically. Hey Shalom. I like him. Okay. I like him. Okay
Yeah
You know you were never gonna be a mod and so you were never gonna be why sweet Pete. What's wrong?
So if you're okay, I heard you're fighting with Bida a little bit. I hope it's everything's okay
What's going on big big wars that I don't even know about I'm sweet Pete give it a rest, right?
Take yourself. You don't got to delete. You don't got it. You don't got to run away. Take some time off like a vacation
That's good advice. Well, yeah, sweet P. No, sweet P. No
Some whoever sweet P. Me sweet P was my first the person sweet P was the first member of this
She's a very sweet woman. She's the first member. She's got a black cat in the picture. She is very nice
Yeah, and she's been you know, you know, we're all sensitive in our own way. And so
She knows when to she knows when to take a break. I'm Alex Murphy
Sometimes people are unpredictable in this YouTube world, and we don't know like, they like, they just act in the ways we don't know until we get confused and then
We need to like separate from people, from like actual people for a while because it's hard to describe it's crazy.
You know what you do, you know what you do, C.P., if it's Joe, you take his name and you put it on block and you never see it again
and you never got to worry about it, and you never talk to, talk about you because he can't see you.
But she makes a stock account and then harasses you
Yeah, I mean Joe's not gonna do anything here
If you click on the name just says block or report
Yeah
Then you be if I don't know if you're a modern are you modern?
Yeah, yeah, you are my so you can't you say I don't know if she can walk
If you are my dad's it's hard to get rid of that person. Yeah
Yeah
It's just like I mean I can't I can't walk people because in my chat because I need to see everything
That's sad in the chat. So a lot this time with psyche on my knee. I'm crazy. That's all blocking this person
This person that person this person this person and I would I'm like before he gives me the wrench back
I'm blocking everybody. I don't like
Yeah, well, yeah, I'm right on my life. I don't got to see them. I don't gotta worry about it
Yep, that's the ability we have right? Yeah, I never understood this bullshit. I don't block shit
You know, oh, you know, I think some people just
Or like, you know, there's people that are attacking other people like when people are attacking I usually will block
Well, you got to do it because you're the you're on the stream. I mean be it but anywhere
I think you could do it by touching the um to stream your chat psyche. You could block it. I don't want to waste my time reading bullshit
This is a cool blanket
Everyone here is mad. It's only one dollar. You got a blankie
Well, that's what it was psyche. That's what I was going to get next. That was the last thing I was gonna get you
I want somebody to chip it the burrito blanket of the rent. I'm I don't want to I don't like to play
It's very cheesy
There's a stupid blanket that looks like a tortilla and I mean it's like okay. I mean it's like I've seen on Amazon
It just looks dumb. I don't want to look like I really don't I mean it's like dummy. It was a funny. It was a funny visual
Hey look at this look at the neon. I love that neon. Look at the neon right there. I love that right there. It's pretty cool
holding a cat that's a sign yeah it's a neon sign yeah
first really see alien neon sign for wall and there's a oh there's a coupon
for a few dollars I'm gonna put you put that right there the quarter or right
before like when you come up to steps and people gonna turn around for walking
that's nice to see it right there like oh that's pretty cool
Yeah, I can have it or it's like, you know, it's like I can have it on my stream too or something
I mean, it's like I'm gonna put in my wishlist
I mean and I'm about to say in the background of the way you usually do your streams that that's what I mean
Yeah, and it's like it's hard because it's like but it's like behind there is like a staircase
It's like I'd have to get like a ladder and hang some stuff up if I hang it on the wall back there, but I can figure it out
I think there's a probably handing. Oh, yeah, there's some cool alien stuff
I like this thing, I like this stuff, it's like a keycap.
Yeah, it's really hard to find where it says
add to the wish list, where is that part?
It says it's like a tiny little,
there it is, add to list.
They make it really hard to find.
Okay, let me see.
Yeah, I'm having fun looking at stuff on Amazon right now.
Because I can actually like
freaking
It looks really good in these houses and stuff like that. I don't know. I really should get that I
Need some more lights and stuff. I got some I think I got some more decks on Timu. I should have some really cool decks coming
Hey, Sam and how are you doing? Hey, Bader? You're still here
You're still here despite being unmodded, right?
Bader was kind of mad, but
It's better not being in law really. It really is. Money is a headache.
Shout out to my guys, Sam.
I am, let me see what else it was.
Oh, there's my open panel. Yeah, oh, we have nice 26 people in chat too.
The time is at 4.30. I'm thinking of like,
I'm thinking of food right now. I'm actually pretty hungry. Good morning everybody.
Yeah, thanks. I'm thinking of also
I'm moving forward like best
Format for this show and you know, it's like I'm getting a kind of like
Irritated with some of these like really really like long endless endless
Open panels. I mean, it's like I mean I love the open panels. I do and it's like I always have I mean
I have the open panel. I'll still have better. I can't oh wait. I think there's um sign
You know those letter signs that glows like in in and like a purplish
About a fact. Let me see if I can show it. Oh got it
No, I don't got in this one fuck, but it's like you put the letters on it
You can put like psyches and we can tell us you can write it and they'll glow
Yeah, so mini version like a fucking McDonald's on something on menu
The lights up you put the letters in front of it
Oh
That's pretty good. They got up. I'm just see if I could find it up. I see to the ball. I was all the other day
I was like, I think you could do good
Yeah, I mean it's like I would like love to give a lot of great price lights on team right now like really like I could probably like
Really fix up love the pace. Hey, I'm salmon
Sweet P. Yep. Sweet P fear the women are created outcome on
Yeah, so guys do you want to do I can do like I can do I can you know you guys can do the AI songs too
I mean, it's really easy to do. It's like super easy. It's like it's like ridiculously easy and it will sound good
I mean it's like
It's pretty funny
But you know if you want me to walk you through it. I mean it's like I'll walk everyone through it
I'll do an example like I'll do a song about somebody
That volunteers or that people want to do a song about
And we can just come up with a few points about it. I can put it through chat GPT then I put it through a
AI music generator with the lyrics
I mean the egg so it's like it's really fast and really easy to do if you know once it's the it done
You know, then you can go on your own. It's like all free
pretty cool things you can do with the
If the technology right who she talking to who
Sweet pea. Sweet pea is talking to
I can beat I think video was saying something about that like I think
Maybe I misunderstood but I was watching I heard her say your name
And that's I'm not ever sure what the context was or what happened with you guys. I just heard
She was upset or something about you
Oh, you're talking to Saki?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, she's talking to me.
It's your sensitive.
It's you stalked me for 24-7.
Yeah.
Good morning, classy sassy.
Good morning.
So...
Got some good stuff to go through, let me see.
She kept asking me to time her out.
Like a weirdo.
Who was who's big? Totally King sexy beta. Oh, is that Rob? Is that you six that sexy Rob?
Right in your dating sweep you right I mean, it's kind of confusing guys. This is like this is like a soap opera
I'm doing good
I don't know. It's like, you know, I mean now he's become there's now he's big tall sexy Vader
And it's the same person and I know he was dating sweet Pete. They haven't seen him for months. Where's he?
Where have you been? Why have you just abandoned my chat?
You could come on my chat sometimes
Okay, I don't even know what the fuck was going on. Okay. I'm sorry. I don't know
I'm I don't know if I didn't answer your question. All I know is that beat is mentioned your name
I'm not sure why you know, that's why people just are saying stuff. Okay, I'm not trying to talk maybe there's two sweet peas
I don't know. I think that's a real sweet pea, right?
Well, yes, you know, they always throw two so
I have no I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe there's misunderstanding probably, you know
Looked confused. Sorry, sweetie. I'm very confused guys. Oh my gosh. You don't think it's Rob. Well, he has the same exact
Big tall sexy king, but maybe not and sweepies that Rob sweepy knows sweepy dated Rob's I still know that build the real Rob sweepy
This week he won't be back
Can you hear that little rhythm with yes or no?
Oh, I'm sorry. I don't mean it. Oh my gosh
Forgot maybe you're not dating him. Okay. Okay. It is a real suit. Okay. I'm sorry. I didn't mean I know you're not dating him
I forgot. I thought you were friends or something. I'm not sure
Dingo you miss the giant broccoli
I just remember they were like friends or something they called in
Oh, these rumors.
I don't know more.
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't get taken anymore.
Why are you mumbling, God?
These rumors.
That's how he reads.
He's a mumbo-rebo.
I do the same thing sometimes.
I'm sorry.
I'm not wide awake like you are.
I didn't get any sleep.
Well, yeah, we're on different schedules, obviously, but you know, you haven't gotten any sleep. Well, you should go to sleep
But now 7 30 a.m.
By the way, you sound just like I sound so what are you talking about mumbo?
Well
Okay, mr. Miss VP please ignore him mr. Sensitive
Okay, it's repeat. Love you guys. I'm trying to do an AI song though
You have to like tell me somebody to do an AI song about I mean I'll do it, but I don't want to do it about think the
You know the
Mormon Scientology on this discord brigade. I don't want to dance
No, I don't want to do I mean I can make and write a song like that in like two seconds, and it'll be fun
That's what I'm saying. I don't want to do that. So that's why I'm asking for suggestions. Well, you throw the names of everybody in the jet
use everybody in the chat's names people that you know
too many it's gonna be too that's too messy it's gonna be too obscure i mean i mean i did a song
with you can make it precise you can make it precise so you could just freestyle this like
it doesn't want to put easy and after actually put yeah don't worry about me don't put me in the
song that's good don't worry about my name is so funny like i said me and god is the two funny ones
doesn't work for us okay i'll just do it i'll just do it later i'll just do it later you know
i think but it is really cool you know what else else um cat tpt is like hey i want to like work
with you on a tarot deck because i just told you i know i was like oh here i have a tarot
told tpt out of tarot tarot do you want about tarot that's a good song a tarot song yeah i mean yeah
i will i can i can you want about tarot i can put people's names in it but um maybe like brainstorm
Come come come do all the terrible people you page who Eric?
Not Emma don't put him in
No, Emma's Emma's Emma's dead to me. Hey, sweetie. I don't know what you know
Sometimes you get mad and stuff like that. It was really nothing personal, but you know, it's like really
It's online, you know, right? I got it. Um, you still got the second every page, right?
Which second there? Oh, yeah, I have another page. Yeah
Why you don't go over there time to time and like you know instead of like always
Well not saying we risk in it
But if you want to play music and stuff and have a little fun nights and change it up
You could go on to the other one. It's not monetized yet. You could just have fun
Yeah
I can like, I mean, for fun, I want us to are having, you know, I can have, I can do members only because all the members are here and stuff like that.
I really want to like put the attention here. You know, I will, I mean, I do have that page, that page is ready to go.
That page is, you know, it's clear of anything. I mean, it's fine. It's good for a backup.
You know, I'm not really like, you know, into like playing music and stuff like that. I'm like in any way like make a channel called psyche after dark
Yeah, but there's a PAT and PAT. Yeah, I mean, this is psyche after dark psyche's playhouse. Yeah, it's too much like Pues
I don't get sued by you know by a column or something. So see a money penguin
Yeah, classy sassy money for 20 years. Okay. I got nothing on this channel. What do you mean? You got nothing on this channel?
What does that mean?
Yeah, I do love Pee Wee. I used to love watching. I was like, I was the perfect age for that show.
I was like, uh...
Pee Wee's Playhouse? Yeah, that was a good one.
And Pee Wee's Big Adventure. That was a classic movie. It was one of the best movies.
Pee Wee meant his character at the groundlings. The groundling is, you know, you know what the
groundling is, right? It's like, uh...
I put my, I saw him backstage. You could see the link there.
Oh, okay.
Oh, you saw yeah, you didn't know it's a big head. Do you sing it?
Yeah, I could sing it but
Listen to it. I'm a pella. Okay. Oh
My god, look God what?
I
Didn't knock me off
Give me a seizure and
I don't like this long but god damn
If you have like if you have epilepsy
Yeah, but it has that effect on people, yeah.
Yeah, it affects Appalachian people.
That shit was pretty new.
That shit got me out of the womb.
What the fuck is happening here?
OK, OK, so let me see.
Where's my list?
OK, now I'm trying.
OK, so.
what happened god is sharing this like one of his he's like he's like video
backstage and it's like it's a little bit not for the week trippy trippy oh I put
a little reading page when you first started streaming but it was fun oh
awesome yeah you want to make sure I'm to subscribe yeah
when he first started so I don't know who you're talking about but yeah make sure you go to
pages channel two because she started streaming on her channel and doing readings there too
it's pretty cool I'll fix this banner there we go then we can put the background in there
I'll get better at this guys I'm just like there's so many
different feeling about to say you feeling dark tonight so go back no nice backgrounds no no and
You know it's good to start field, you got to start field.
Or you like to start field, like this one right here, hold on, no it's this one right here.
Yeah it starts with the lines, I like the one with the lines if I'm right, that one
there.
That's good, that's good, I like that, that's the one, that's a good one.
Okay, okay, that's the job.
Perfect. Oh play the song
Christine
Okay, can somebody play this song? It's on the something about it's on the
Talking about my song actually. Okay, that's
I don't know if we can play you but you can if you want the link to it. I'll post the link to it
It's like, you know, I don't think you really want
No, no, I'm only kidding. I'm only kidding. It's the private chat. I'll put it in the main pad if you want
Copy it
Okay here guys you want to be the guys here's here's the guys like not gaudy
song you know she wants the actual the AI song okay yeah I want to play it but
guys it's on the um it's on the about and guys can someone play it for like
on getting God play it or the song I create okay well I'll just I'll play off
the off my phone I think I have to put it up to my
Let's see
Flipping carts under neon lights
Baited dreams in late night fights
Summer's laugh cuts through the smoke
And Christine always finds the joke
Arthur's ghost in a digital haze. Electro-smile lighting up the maze.
Open panel, nothing's ever planned. Just arts on sleeves and raised hands.
It's a circus, it's a prayer. It's a quiet truth, laid bare.
One minute left, the next is born.
Flirty diamond got us poor bong bong, but sometimes we all belong in this weird and twisted song.
This is the Psyche Awakens song.
Bader cries while the chat goes wild, Pedro's eyes, but she's big guy.
Everyone's got a story to sell, but no one leaves and cares to sell.
All the silly things, and we shout all our words.
But behind every screen is a broken dream.
It's a circuit, it's a prayer, it's the quiet truth, lady, that I don't want in love's indexed form
It's a pretty diamond that has fallen, bum, bum, bum, but somehow I belong in this weird, twisted song
The lecture's gone, still we see her tonight
In every green-lighted night
Christmas holds us when it rains
And some of this is through the flames
Okay, so that's it amazing. Okay, so it's cute. It's a cute song
My favorite part of that whole beautiful song
That I was the funniest part that was funny. I'm not crying, but I'm gonna figure out ways
That was the funniest part to me. I remember it hit me. That shit hit me just now like
Listening to him like we I remember that for the diamond part. I was yeah, I'll put this I'll put I'll put her in the next
Where is it
I'll listen to okay, so it's money for 20. All you have to do is go to go to oh, where's the song you listen to it to go to the
description of the channel. It's posted there. It's one of the links there. Oh my gosh, I'm
sideways. It's one of the links in the, it's in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in
the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in the, in
Yes, we like yeah, so it's one was like oh sweepy good take a break
But sweepy disappeared like for months like already like three months or something. She just came back
So we're hoping like people will say
I
Forgot oh, I forgot fozzy. Oh fozzy a fozzy and Romeo are wrestling
Guys, it'll be great. It's really easy to do by the way
It's really really easy to do like basically you just
Like it doesn't work all seamlessly through the chat GPT. You have to just like ask you that GPT to write lyrics about something
Then you plug those lyrics into the AI music generator and tell them the kind of
Music you want and then I'll just make it in like 30 seconds
Pretty cool
PPU can time out player cap for 24 hours. Yeah, it's pretty nice. It's like that was your first try. Yeah
Well, and actually like the song someone made me an Elisa Jordana AI song like
And I posted that on my my channel. I had it like I'm private right now
But yeah, so someone did it so that's that kind of like it kind of like tinned me off to it
And then it's like I've been talking to the chat GPT and the chat GPT is like
I'll be back up. Yeah, you need to go serve somebody in the in need. I don't know if he wants to come on
You follow up or yeah
To test CPT is really smart. You can talk to it like you can talk to it now
It will like remember what you say and then it will
Tell you things it can do it would suggest things like hey, I can do this for you
Don't mean to do this doing do this and we'll do a lot of stuff like
Great graphic. I'll show you the graphic it did
Oh, I'm listening to your psyche, but I also got the music to be low.
Well, God, look at this.
This is a little bit sorry.
Yes, very easy job.
Too bad everybody can sing it.
So the photos here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Is this tapping into a power that everybody don't know how to use that AI school is fucked. Oh
It is did you drop everyone's name? Yeah, thank you so much. Okay. Thank you so much for dropping those links
Yeah, and yeah, we're really giving me about supporting other people here and helping other people
Especially it's missing a panel
the
Yeah
I know what app was that that's I sent that I sent it the other day when I was swiping it's um
Oh, you ever wanted to kiss your crush? That's the one that's the app
He did pops up like that and then they show two people with two pictures you take a picture you take another picture and meet
them kiss
Both. Oh, yeah. Yeah. It was crazy. They had to pay for that. They had to die.
So they went out they way to pay for that. So you should
Yeah, but it's like 10 bucks for like what a month and it was for you know, it's they put in a video
So it's you know, it kind of like it's
Let's see so we're white noise. Oh, I have a white noise. Let me see. I mean
I have a let me see the moon. Where's the moon right now? So the moon right now is
is waning. Next phase at July 17th will be a Pisces on July 15th. It says Pisces,
Moons and Pisces. Okay, so this brings in a piece of emotions and a receptivity
to other people's feelings.
You have a desire to be of help and maybe willing to sacrifice something for the sake of others.
Your emotions predominate over common sense, so it's better to do things which require imagination and inspiration rather than reason and cool logic.
Your body may be more responsive than usual to alcohol, drugs, and medicine, so beware of overdoses.
Poor quality food could also give you a touch of food poisoning.
I don't know if that's specific to me. Let me see.
I don't know a easy pick a number one to ten
Infinite
All right, and that's like you pick one two
Nine all right nine. Okay. I'll see you guys
Okay, I need you
You love
God I was
Pick a number pick a number. All right. See you guys
Yeah
Would you go say 80 now second the way or 89 days?
Well, I just think at eight, you know, nine times eight is like seventy-two, seven plus two is nine, you know, just like every
everything
multiply in the
times table, like what equal to nine, if it's times nine?
I don't know, like they're weird.
Anything times nine, yeah, five times nine, it's gonna, it's gonna, the number, the result will end and like will add up to nine every time.
Yeah, just like that movie 23, everything added up to 23.
Yeah, I kind of like that
But yeah, but it's like it actually is a thing in math. It's like a mathematical thing. I think in 23 that was just like, you know
And then to two divided by three is point six six six
Okay, I have the
This is just what I need to do. I need to grab your coffee and hit that motherfucking link it hurt
Is it pen people the psyche forgets to pin it they should need to drop it
That's why nobody came up here. Oh, yeah, I said down the way to get on my
YouTube on this. I was thinking I'm like, hold on. Is it pen?
They're peanut. I don't think it is. I don't think you pin the psyche. I'm not sure
So when you drop down, I don't know if you pinned it
No late pin there you go. That's why nobody's covered up Sykes
I'm over that one with me. You and God. He's just having a conversation. Nobody want to come up
Yeah
Miss Leia good morning miss Christine. Good morning, mr. Money good morning. I mean damn it see it's broken off
Okay, so
Okay, go to my shop and
Okay, I have a few I downloaded a bunch of these YouTube apps on this tablet and like one of them was a or the chats on this
Okay, so I can post the chat here
Hey, we got wait for a second. He's doing it right now. Yeah, don't worry about it. Then you go switch over you can go pin it
Everybody got everybody right now. You know, they're gonna fly and after that link drop
A link drop will go pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink,
I'm hungry now. I'm ready for like food. What are you ready for? What are you
ready for? Yesterday, I had um,
oh, good. My neighbor's brought me a couple of burritos yesterday, but I kind of made
them move for like breakfast kind of food in the coffee. Oh my gosh. Okay. 25 people
Yeah, you gotta you gotta have coffee in the blood in the morning. That's just me
I was too drunk last night. I didn't hardly smoked. I think I smoked like two blunts. That's it
Turn it up now. You heard y'all. Have your coffees and
Listen to them music
Do it all by myself
What's up got that perp right up. It's happening. What's up got put your own in my tub
I got mad music in my ear while I'm listening to psyche
Snap your fingers do you stay? Oh
You can't stop laughing you mean that's good. Yeah, we're even around when she said she was not even on YouTube
I don't know if I'm looking at old chats. Okay
Okay, a story a tale of Zeus as a goose. Oh, I want to hear that story. I'll have to look at
Let's probably leave in this one
And Zeus turns into a goose
Okay
Let's open right now
Winner
15% and I need another cup of coffee, so I'll be back in a few let me let my phone already. All right
Open now
There's one restaurant that's open
Pretty funny. Oh, you're not talking about me
You always look at my comments at the wrong time and think about you
I just wanted to come here and because I thought I'm sorry. I don't I don't want to I'm sorry. I always screw things up
I'm sorry. I
Don't I
Know I read the comments the wrong time. I know I'm terrible. Okay, so
So let's read some, it's a little interesting, let me find some here.
We were having some fun reading some of these books yesterday.
Just wait until, there's quite more on YouTube, you're going to go live.
So I'm looking at this book, it's kind of an interesting book.
I don't know. I just go where the wind takes me right now. So let's see.
Well, right now, it's about, OK, it says,
in the 1930, over 1,506 months old,
Los Angeles black and Hispanic infants
were given an experimental measles.
Never informing parents of the potential harm revealing ongoing testing on poor communities.
Without a doubt, an outside influence is sought in the very beginning, and every way continues to seek to maintain control by engineered chaos on a much larger scale.
Without this type of creative confusion, the controller would not thrive and continue to survive to this present day.
The ego is a very powerful and operates in the realm of self-preservation.
Ego, when used for the good of humanity, is a spark of deity.
However, it is not being used for good.
We are here to learn to love, however, evil believes we are here to instead learn hate.
The mind has had its seat in and over the brain.
The spirit has a seat in the divine ego, or God's spark, and has its seat in the spirit.
In two excerpts from chapter 5, the constitution of main sacred text that is written, the constitution
of man is therefore, in essence, a spark of the divine fire.
If further reads, the ego is the man during the human state of evolution.
He is the nearest correspondence, in fact, he is the ordinary unscientific conception
of the soul.
He lives unchanged except for the growth from the moment of individualization until humanity
is transcended and merged into divinity.
He is in no way affected by what we call birth and death.
What we commonly consider as his life is only a day in life
The body which we see the body which is born and dies is a garment which he puts on for the purpose of certain
part of his evolution I
Begin reading a path on found it on faith
Trusting and believing the position I had been placed and had been ultimately good meaning
The experiences and suffering were not in vain.
All things were working together for God, for those who love God became my motto.
It was my hope that with many others to assist by exposure of the hidden evil.
Obviously, there are those who do not share this belief and are held bent in this polar
existence of good and evil or checkered existence who endeavor to create a whole different reality.
This is proven without a doubt by the bombardment of the decisive Luciferian agenda unfolding
everywhere we turn a stated sex playing a profound role in the scheme.
By cultists to be extremely potent and can be channeled for magical purposes, as was factually a practice used by Alistair Crioli.
Magic in the context of Alistair Crioli's Thelima is a term used to differentiate the cult from stage theatrical magic.
and is defined as the science and art of creating change to occur in conformity with will,
including both mundane acts of will as well as ritual magic or more definitive electromagnetism's
mental and physical control. Crowley, a student of ritual magic, wrote that it is theoretically
any change which the object is capable by nature.
In other words, both the negative,
which typically lays dormant and positive within
can be manipulated.
Little known to the average individual,
Alistair Crowley was the heart
of one of the most influential movements
of the 20th and 21st centuries.
Through a secret society,
he founded and named the Ordo Temple Orientes, OTO.
He was very highly regarded and connected to the British M15, the British equivalent of the US FBI, which the M16 said to be comparable to the US CIA.
Crowley's understanding of occult magic and practices also connected and involved him with the goals of the global elite.
Okay, it gets into kind of some darker stuff. Okay, so I don't want to read some of that.
But it is interesting, you know, you might want to check out this book. It's called Deceived Beyond Belief
Yeah
into some interesting stuff. It says,
Behold, I send you out as sheep in the midst of wolves,
to be wise as serpents, and innocent as doves.
Symbolically, a maze is designed to challenge our direction and choices in
life. The purpose of a movement through the maze
is to find our true selves and our place in the grand scheme of this
existence and our role in the world. And hopefully, it's to make the world a
better place. In general, the greater the understanding,
the greater the delusion, the more intelligent, the less
So, yeah, I mean, some of these books will go, you know, all over the place it says,
with the attention of dehumanizing the targets and naming them as inferior, you know, propaganda
successfully created widespread anti-criminal campaign which laid down the foundation to
The fact that these types of tackles are nothing new and will be in the fabric of America and have been quite used quite effectively for many years
That's a real secret, right?
Okay, yeah
Okay, okay
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
California has been a historic state of mind control testing and the forerunner.
You know that, California?
Okay.
It says, what do they want?
Have you ever thought about something you never share with anyone and believe the thought was between you and God?
Have you ever been angry at someone and thought I could
You know unalive them, right?
And only a temporary emotional expression only knowing that you would not do such a thing
Have you ever reminisced about the past and experiences which were designed to help you
advance and grow emotionally and shape your perspective positively and the thoughts that
were used against your mind?
You through mind reading software today with the advancement of mind reading technology a staple in remote neural monitoring programs and programming
capability from numerous operation center setups across the USA and globally
This is no longer fiction, but scientific nonfiction and the prison system is full of these deems undesirables
Okay, the aspects of mind programming reported nationwide and globally by many reveals the
global paradigm to the predictive programming definition and citing an action that causes
a predictive reaction, anchoring definition, the development of mind programming foundations,
conditioning definition, establishing a strengthened, strengthening neural pathways during repetition.
Trigger definitions strong reactionary mind programming related to particular premise
association associative programming i.e. guilt by association discrediting by association
Rationalization used in psychological warfare to persuade belief and behavioral modification. I mean there's a lot of different parts to it, right?
belief
projection perception
Occulted NLP mind programming
There's a lot of, there's a lot to programming, right?
So here's a few examples of how remote neural monitoring is being used on TI or targeted individuals, right?
It says, you decided to go to the store or the gym. The operator targeting you, listening decides
it is the perfect time to beam your legs and cripple you so that you will be unable to walk.
The success is in them listening to the targets thoughts about the pain they're inflicting, letting the operation know that they're
effective in what they're doing and it's working and useful.
I mean, they have this technology.
It's really, really quite frightening.
It's that they have this technology
that can do to think of a voice to skull
where they can actually put like thoughts
in people's head,
and there's something called the God voice.
People think it's the voice of God.
It's called BOG.
And so, I mean, they honestly can,
but it's like, you don't want to, you know,
maybe like put, you know, tin foil over your head,
but maybe lining some in your hat, maybe, I'm not sure.
And then it gets into some things that I just can't say on this show, but you know, you
might maybe find this book, it says, live the love frequency, there is no greater frequency
Evil has run its course, and those in allegiance to it know the time is running out.
Thus they are wreaking global havoc.
Remain faithful, soon they will regrettably understand that the fruitless escalations
of all the visible engenders are just fruitless.
It's interesting.
But it just goes into how love is the highest frequency.
And so basically you can combat all of this with love.
Okay, so now it is 5 a.m.
So let me see if the influx is open to E yet.
I mean, they have pre-order starting.
Open now.
Okay.
McDonald's is opened, Jack in the Box is opened.
Ooh
The bagel place is open so I know his bagels or they I wish they had you they have garlic bagels here that'd be awesome
Watch a
Sam it wants his nova locks. Yeah
Okay, I'm going to get it from this other place and I'm going to get it from the island.
It's cheaper.
Move the locks.
And the brunch box.
I don't know.
Brunch special, that's it.
And a coffee.
A little Bruce shake.
Ice.
Laquillado.
Do that.
Large.
Happy Monday, 20 bucks.
Oh, shit.
I'm hungry.
Money 20, that's the, so it would be money for 20, okay, so.
You crappy Monday. It's a nice Monday. I go there in person. I think it would be much less expensive
free sausage a move
Dunkin Donuts the only day the word happy works is Friday. Yeah, maybe
But, you know, I don't mind Mondays because
How's the jack-in-the-box breakfast? Is it good?
We have these T-Pain munchie meals
Burger Tater
Melt
Regular curry fries, stuffed cookie, and a regular, that's a stuffed cookie
I'm not saying that you're a good old friend of yours.
So, hey Miguel, how are you? Okay.
So what else is interesting? It says,
it kind of talks about some side-offs. Okay.
This is an Aesop's fable played out by mind-invasive technological challenges focused on humanity
scientifically as the battle of strong wild strong wind challenges the sun's appearing subtly and
harmless influence. The fact is we were both control-oriented in the battles for our minds.
And then so you know
kind of this person is kind of get into like
Any person with low self-esteem is susceptible to attacks from the evil when you don't think highly of yourself
And the things you do you are likely to let somebody else run things if you don't like control your mind somebody else will
This is our choices are darkness or light good or evil lover hate negative or positive in the polar state of this existence as the evolutionary process continues
The program particularly focuses on emotions of strong fear or hate.
The control mechanism deliberately creates an environment on earth that is as traumatized as possible and we are bombarded with negativity daily.
This is continued control of humanity that is being set up at each other by creating conflicts, bloodshed, and raging wars.
So, I mean, half this book sounds a little bit unhinged, and half of it sounds like love, makes a lot of sense, you know, I've been cheated by a few of them, too.
But that's a little bit, I basically went through the whole book, just that.
I was reading some interesting stuff yesterday.
Like, Ovid.
I had this book called the Devil's Toolkit. I'll read a chapter of it. It says...
When I when I and those who are like me into your life, this is HG Tudor
He is a narcissist and so he writes about narcissism and stuff like that
But he is a narcissist and so he has he's a British in case we said when I
When I and those who are like me into your life. We appear like an angel everything
We touch is made wonderful a golden light shines from us
Which you will find captivating and enthralling our words sound like a heavenly orchestra, which is playing just for you
We show you such a perfect love we wrap you in our arms and tell you
how we will always protect you and shield you from the darkness.
The world becomes a brighter and more wonderful place because of our arrival.
Yet, for all that we appear have been sent, we came from a far darker place,
and by the time you have experienced the denigration, the devaluation,
and the hurt and the misery, you will refer to us by many names.
Our behavior towards you convinces you that we have been possessed by demonic forces.
Our agenda is foul, filled with vitriol and malice.
You eventually, and it may take considerable time for you to reach this, realize that although
we appear as angels, we are really the devil's lieutenants.
So it says, we are narcissists. Our sole purpose is to walk the earth and gather fuel.
At first, this is done by extracting fuel of a positive nature from the love admiration
and praise that you will shower us in.
This never proves enough, and it is then that we return to the harvesting of negative fuel,
a supply of fuel that arises from anger, anguish, misery, upset, and dejection.
Whatever a bane emotion is to be had, we will cause it to manifest and then drink deep of
the fuel that flows from it.
hurtfulness and cruelty that give us the greatest power. In order to tap into the sources of negative
fuel, we must utilize several different tools and instruments to assist us. Some of these tools
bring forth the fuel. Others are designed to prevent the loss of the fuel. Many types of people use
these instruments of darkness, but there is a set that is dedicated to the dark art of narcissism.
available to our kind will be utilized by our kind, and they are nevertheless, but they
are nevertheless.
We are always looking to add up this arsenal that we carry with us, and it causes a considerable
delight when we find a further tool that suits our malign purposes.
Okay, if you've been entangled with a narcissist and you may recognize some of these instruments,
though you may not know precisely why the narcissist deploys them against you, others
may be unaware of it and it's only by reading this book that you'll realize what the malicious
utensils are being applied to ruin your life.
fulfill the narcissist quest for fuel. The journey through these tools and the narcissist uses,
as explained by a narcissist, is to revive you with unparalleled insight and understanding
as to what the narcissist does with these instruments and why. By gaining understanding about
these dark devices are used against you, you will be able to remain vigilant in their use,
May be able to begin to avoid or diminish their effect on you. I will explain each of these instruments in my
customary direct style you may not find it comfortable
Reading but then engaging with the narcissist is ultimately never a smooth ride is it?
Ready yourself for revelation and insight. As I turn the key inside the lock, lift the lid and allow you to look upon these weapons of darkness.
This is a medley of manipulative instruments each narcissist has at his or her disposal. This is the devil's toolkit.
I'll read you this one chapter, the first chapter. So it says the saw of interruption.
It says, the saw of interruption is a device that is direct and cutting, and it is used
to cut you off when you are speaking or doing something.
I must be the center of your attention, I must be the star of the show.
I am the sun and you are all the planets that revolve around me, asking the life-giving
radiance of my rays.
Everything I say is important, everything I do is interesting, I have been set up on
This applies to all of my kinds. Some of them will be famous entertainers,
some stars of stage and screen, musicians, singers, actors, comedians who literally take
center stage in order to entertain the masses. Highlighted in that dazzling spotlight they allow
They're challenged to be witnessed by the world at large and in return they drown in
a sea of admiration and attention.
It is massively edifying.
Sports stars, television presenters, politicians and celebrities are represented heavily among
star kinds.
They are all demanding the time and the spotlight and attention.
They entertain you.
They inform you.
They lead you.
They return for these blessings.
You must give them attention and adulation.
innovation, invention and progress.
These people who have taken on the mantle
of huge responsibility to get the job done
to deliver these products and services
that you can eat and drink, be kept warm,
be sheltered and be entertained
by the technology has to offer.
I'm referring to the CEOs of corporations,
the chairman of the board, the entrepreneurs
and business angels.
These people are drawn from our ranks
and they make the world a better
and more interesting place.
They stand for, they stand for, I'm sorry, okay.
Okay, they stand head and shoulders above you. They must be from our kind as otherwise the job would not get done.
It is only our kind that can remain focused on the end result.
It is only us that are able to live with the maxim that the end always justifies the means.
We are untroubled by the very things that hold back progress.
and remorse are of no concern to us. These are things which are
for no purpose to our kind. We have been stripped of such feelings and in turn
this frees us to achieve what must be done.
We have a job and we deliver you admire this single-purpose vision
You are aware of the driven nature by which we live our lives
But in order to keep the world turning this is what we must do the members of our club had these positions of leadership and
Responsibility for anyone else would not have been able to fulfill their roles effectively
What has gotten into me. Oh, yeah, so it's funky. This is a book this is about
This is written by a narcissist. And so he's telling you the things that his is like
Point of view. Okay. It's interesting. His name is HG2. He's a very interesting. Okay
So the result is that what our kind has to say is worth listening to by contrast
What you have to say is of no use or interest
The only thing that you speak we will listen is when you are providing us with our well-deserved praise and admiration
Our achievements and our superiority mean we are entitled to be admired, to be loved, and to receive plodded after plodded.
If you are not doing this and your words are pointless and they must be stopped, this is when we apply the saw of interruption.
We wield it to shut you up in a vicious and sudden manner. There is no gentle admonishment or subtle...
coercion to bring about your silence. This is not applicable. What we want for you is to be quiet and for you to fall into this
silence straight away. Consequently, the sob and eruptions apply and with simple, swift,
silent actions, we have silenced you. By cutting off what you're saying, we are also able to reinforce our superiority.
We emphasize you are inferior to us because you have nothing worth saying. This is about the silent action results.
in you feeling belittled and worthless which accords with our overall design to keep reducing
your sense of self-worth and your self-esteem. We do not want you feeling stronger capable. We
want you weak and malleable so that our continued application of the tools from our toolkit yields
the results we want. Cutting you off when you are speaking is a very effective means of letting you
and others who may be listening who is in control. You are allowed to speak by our grace and if we
saying is unproductive. Namely, it is not giving the fuel that we require. We shall cut
you off. The indignant glare that you will provide also serves to fuel us as we deem
treatment of your emotional response to us cutting you off. Should you try and speak
again when it is necessary, then the saw can be wheeled straight away with a minimum of
Kind of crazy, huh? I mean the link and yet. Yeah, so that's kind of I mean they have so they have like the sob and eruption
Then he has like the hammer of what's it called? It's called the hammer of something the hammer of of the chisel of misery and the hammer of
Intimidation, I mean there's all these tools. I mean they're of course metaphorical, right? But
These are the devil's toolkit, but if you were aware of these, you know, then you're
Less likely to be affected by them. So how is everyone to a 20 people on chat? That's awesome because it is very early
I'm looking for something in red
You heard that song it's a beautiful country song. Yeah, these books are good. These are HD tutor. He is
British and he also has a YouTube channel and he is super
Super good, like, you know, really interesting
He's very he's very shameless narcissists, but
Stainless narcissists can be interesting. It's be especially because he shares the information. Okay, let me see
Okay, I was like the best deal.
What a dingle shit.
Okay, um...
It's like a butterfly.
Okay, free browse.
You can make anything you want, Vicky, it's easy.
Ooh, oh my gosh, look what they have in place
called Ziggy's Coffee.
You look at Ziggy's Coffee.
Three dollars out, 15 dollars.
Okay, so I'm not sure if they'll talk up.
Did I cover Joe already?
No.
Well, there's only a few plays to open right now.
Oh, Cookie's banana pudding.
That looks really good.
or do they have it all that all they have in this place is banana pudding
they just have banana pudding all they have is it's one restaurant
i mean it's pretty good but hello cat lover let's see they have a cinnamon
dip so they're hitting the dons open this place has
farmer boys there's open farmer boys let's see breakfast burrito
that's decent do they have coffee subject to bicky and spunky oh awesome
But they do have coffee, coconut iced coffee, something like that.
Jack in the box.
The student part is worse because I added out the part, uh, lapping and talking spunky, okay.
Sea used coffee.
Is it all iced?
Selection here
Frozen campfire
Oh, okay, okay beef and potato burrito that sounds good
Actually, I have the burritos for my I have my neighbor's burritos like I see coffee actually
Awful sandwich
Give me two burritos. They're like really famous
Don't want you don't make videos and you don't want people making messing with you. I know I know you feel cat lover. You know, it's like, you know
It's definitely
it's crazy invasions these days not only of
Privacy but people actually like taking they'll take a streamers like head like they'll take their face
And they'll put it on like a for now and stuff like that. They will
They will swap things, they will take one minute of your voice, and they will make you say anything.
They will, you see, they made me kiss Joe.
It looks like I'm kissing Joe, people think I'm kissing Joe.
It looks like it, and it appears like I'm kissing Joe.
It's an illusion, but it does.
I mean, to all, let me know, you know, okay.
You just saw that, it's okay.
Cat lover, okay, yeah.
Some people will get triggered by, you know, because they've been, you know,
They've been, you know, I know some people have had nudes shared and, right? So, you're
picky alone, right? Okay. So, the Ziggy's coffee sounds pretty good, okay? But it sounds,
oh, how, like, expensive. It has a $10 coffee. What the fuck? They're looking gold. You know,
AI kissing was a thing. Yeah. It's all gold. Can you make me kiss you? I want to see that.
So build my own munchie meal.
$12.
You're the ultimate cheater.
It's nice that you can sandwich two tacos.
Coffee, coffee?
Yep, you can get a coffee.
I'll wait I'll wait up until six. Oh, let's see what else.
there's boba sex page okay so what do we have here
what have we here hey page how are you good to see ya
we should all add drawings to the book as full yeah we we will we will we're gonna
guys I want like everyone to do art AI songs so you know what I mean it's like
guys we can have a whole creative
community of you know it's like pretty cool stuff coming through you know be
very creative and the whole whole lot of you know progress so let's see
book called Quid Proquo.
You don't mean to be rude,
but I think you should ask before you link
at someone's channel.
I mean, really, I mean, if they have a channel,
I think, you know, there should be links, but whatever.
So I'll read some, I'll read some of the fables,
A-Subs fables, this is really short, short and sweet.
Oh, I might have read, I didn't read all these yesterday.
There's a book of signs and symbols,
omens, tire game, ready for work.
You're having a time, obviously you're having a time.
Yeah, I saw, I was watching.
I was like, you know, you guys were having some fun laughing.
I was like, she was laughing so hysterically.
I was picturing Sam in a mosh pit or something.
It was pretty funny.
She was laughing so hysterically.
let's see yeah I think I'm going to be starting to read some of these chat
GPT books I want to get really good at chat GPT because it will be so useful for
like doing a lot of stuff doing a lot of stuff it's a few years ago when I was
using it it wasn't as good and now it seems like it's ready to ready to go yeah
So, let's see, yeah, we've got some interesting books.
I do have about 10,000 books, so just bear with me.
A lot of them are free. You can get free books on Amazon by the way all day
Yeah, some of the channels do have zero content, so if you can do it, you're careful, but let's see what we have.
We have some interesting stuff.
The superhuman mind, free of, okay, real history of the earth.
Oh, here we have the origins of words and everything between.
This sounds interesting. Names, words, and everything between.
Okay, so it does have a lot of definitions. Okay
When you get subscribers use deleted accounts, what do you mean?
Okay
Try this blue one
Let me check on Benny. See if he's lively. I don't know he's been up on that
Okay.
I think this is a pain to read.
You know, with difficult people,
I'm just gonna save that one for sure.
We're becoming a creative genius again. Benny's camera's pointed at the ground. Yeah, she's probably asleep
Uh, I can't figure out a playlist. Um, you can
And Benny's left because she has 5 to 500 people watching. That's crazy. That's a lot. That's awesome
Whoo
Love these books like am I the asshole get your shit together, which please
Everything I need to learn I learned from the Twilight Zone
I'm understanding cults
What's your favorite Charo deck? I love the Rider Wape, right? But I like the Toth,
but I love these other decks too. I love like the Disney decks are awesome.
There's just so much beauty and information in every deck.
Pistia, Sophia, a lot of this on cats and chaos, cats, cows.
If you have a three car reading, would I read?
OK.
I love that one.
Here is a very good idea. Maybe Vicky wants a card. Yeah, anybody wants a card?
Okay
We're gonna know just what's in the stars for
If the stars line for you and Bikki, okay.
Okay, okay.
Meet, shuffle, and I'll, okay, I'm gonna do that for you.
And then I'll, then I'll do you, cat.
Cat lover, because I know I've done a few reads for you.
Recently, so I wanna get everyone ahead of having,
I'm in some bulbous tech,
you wanna know if the stars line for you and Bikki, okay.
Okay, interesting. So we have this two of coins. So this says you could practically kind of come
together and balance each other. Somehow you maybe make a good balance, but it's like, I don't know,
it seems like maybe she's carrying more of the thing, but she looks like she's part of the plan.
She, I don't know, she's loading you up or something like that.
Who is this?
Oh, this is Vicky.
Okay.
And then we have the three of coins.
So this could be, so we have the two point and three of points.
It's like 23, right?
Coming together right then coming leaving partying with more also the three is the third party situation
Maybe coming together with the other person to in the relationship, which is packing stuff leaving. I don't know
She looks like she's about to light a bonfire or something. I'm not sure completely, but they're interesting one straight
I'll get for cat
Love some breakfast together. Okay, okay, okay
Cat I see even heart broken up. I think I've got that card for you to before too and the queen of coins. Okay
This is your power couple. This is you, and you're looking for a pirate, right?
You're looking for a pirate because you had your heart broken in the past, right?
Oh, you feel like every, but now you're interested in somebody. Is he looking at you?
Look, he's looking at you. You don't even see him. Your eyes close right there.
He's a nice guy, too. He's not like evil like Captain Hook. He's like sweet. He might be a little bit of a drinker, too.
Is that them? I don't know. I think that's for like, you know, Kat, I think that's like, you know, her and some guy that looks interested in her.
You like these? Yeah, the villains deck. I'm getting another, I have the Alice deck. I also have some decks coming soon.
Oh, Timo, he's on Techie Smash 420.
So let's see what happens.
Now I think the food is starting to open up, deals.
I might just have to go for that Ziggy's coffee.
I mean, sounding pretty good right now.
Or jack-in-the-box, yeah
We have a Phil's coffee five dollars off 14 other than the coffee's really good. I think all they have is coffee
You don't know I'm in jack-in-the-box for breakfast. Yeah, I'll skip it. Yeah, it's not that great
I'm thinking of this
Mean there's no place open right now. It's like they have the banana banana putting place
They have Carl's, Jr. They have a cinnamon roll place
Plays looks pretty good, but
All they have is cinnamon rolls. That's all
McDonald's they have free item on 15, which is what would it be? It would be free
What would it be see item tell you
Okay, Farmer Boys is gonna have that copy. It has copy. Okay, I'll drink. I'll get some
from Farmer Boys. A breakfast box, cage-free egg, hand-cracked and scrambled, topped with a
I'll get an extra coffee hot coffee
You're a dingle, okay, I'll get extra coconut
I could I want that
Simmer to cover now, it's gonna be too expensive on a 250 20% off so that's five dollars off
I got one coffee.
Night work.
Vanilla ice coffee.
Cold foam.
You don't know many Aquarius people?
I'm an Aquarius Moon and Aquarius is a
Very good good sign, you know, it's like
We're a little bit alien to the zodiac. We're like a little bit mostly detached
Basically the moon the moon signs
Now I'm thinking I'm gonna get maybe some doughnuts
You guys like donuts?
Boy, there's one.
Let's see.
They have donuts available.
Dunkin' donuts, yep.
Six dollars off 20, that's a good deal.
Okay, so.
I can get.
We're all kind of weird hot. I need to get I'm like I need to eat something. Okay the ice macchiato that looks great. Okay
Large regular, okay whole milk
Hi, hi, babe. Hi, babe
There's Lenore
All right Jake the ice dunkelet
Dunkelet, okay
Okay, that sounds good
And what else do I get?
Like a half a dozen donuts, that should be enough.
I can get a Boston cream.
Glaze Bruiser.
Hi babe, hi.
Strawberry frost with sprinkles.
Star Spangles.
Jelly.
Oh my god.
And look at two jelly.
It sounds so good.
Okay.
$13.
How does that sound guys?
Okay, it came out to you
Oh, I'm gonna get it because it took up like six bucks
Okay, and I deserve it
my tracks my tracks don't want to say hi if you don't want to hi oh hi
the brother's a Virgo we barely get along oh oh shit yeah um
Okay, so you we're gonna want to check out your like your son's sign and your moon sign
Okay, so the Sun sign is like your masculine side sometimes it represents the father
Okay, and then the moon sign is the feminine side or the emotional side
So sometimes it represents the mother too
The moon sign is often for women more
pronounced. They both are, and the Sun, of course, is always going to be standing out,
but the women have the stronger connection to the Moon, right? And it does to their emotions
and that kind of thing. Is the link 10, you guys? Did I turn the link?
Yeah, and so you're gonna want to check out your moon sign and it's like you know
You have to kind of know when you were born your exact time to kind of just know for sure your moon sign
But sometimes it can change over a period of a day
Do I feed stray cats?
Me your Scorpio with Pisces rising. What does that mean? Okay?
Pisces rising and moon sign. Okay, so your Pisces rising and
Okay, so you have a lot a lot of water in your chart Katie a lot of water
from what I see so far they pick you so Scorpio water sign and Pisces, you know a water sign and
The rising in the moon, okay, so the moon is the
Moon is a water sign, right and
Yes Pisces
Your Scorpio with Pisces rising. Okay, so Scorpio. Okay, so Scorpio is a water sign, right? So your Scorpio sun and
Let's see, in me, my sister, in law, in me, in nephew, it's got, okay, so you have a lot of emotion going on there.
Yeah, you can, well, you can bulbous because there's the ascendant, there's the moon and there's the sun, but there's also a lot of other signs too.
I mean, it's like, there's a lot of stuff, we all kind of focus on the sun.
That's basically the traditional astrology.
People will say, oh, that's just a fun sign.
You know, a lot of placements and a lot of everything means things, the house it's in.
So it's a whole lifetime of study basically, you know, you can study for a long time.
I've had some professionals have done to you.
Hi babe, hi, how are you?
So guys, I'm at 96 members, I think I'm at 94 memberships, 94 memberships, and then I will be at 100, when I get to 100, I will have 14 emojis.
You're gonna eat breakfast? Okay, good. Yeah, you have a lot of emotion. Yeah, I mean it sounds like
I would say you know
See what your ascendant is or he said rising home. He said he had a rising home. So they Scorpio and then
Pisces rising and
Okay, well, yeah, so those those are the three main main ones, you know
so
Rule by Neptune is Pisces a rule by Neptune you get them Neptune you get the moon
It's gonna be an emotional time and you're gonna maybe find somebody with
The right elements to compliment you give a lot of water maybe a lot of fire that
Or a lot of earth
Pisces you know yep and guys. Oh, yeah, I have
more more emojis to insert to into the
You in Gemini people don't get along Gemini they would do any cuss throughout. Yeah, that's the air. It's the air will mess with that water
Kind of like, you know, come like a tempest tempest in a teapot, you know, it's like just like a stormy weather
You can in your camps sometimes
So, I hope you guys enjoy his hanging out, you know, just doing different stuff.
I have so many really cool things to share with you guys, but I don't, I need like,
so now I need feedback to know it's like you guys are enjoying it, because it's in
the stuff that's pretty weird.
Okay.
I haven't been collecting these books for quite a while, so what is this book?
Pretty interesting science fiction, I don't know if there will be one like that, so I'll go back a little bit.
I've collected so many books, yep.
Anyhow, I'm ready for those donuts.
What's the best sign of, okay, so, what's the best sign to get along with, okay, so for KT, KT, and, okay, yeah.
I would say, I don't know, do you say that you won't get along with Gemini?
Me, I don't know, me and Gemini people don't, so Vicki doesn't get along with Gemini.
Well, I think you might get along with Gemini, because Gemini, the air can work really well with the water.
It can.
Otherwise, it's bound, like, it's too much fire and water.
It's like, you know, the water can put out fire, you know.
I think the air is the good way to go because it just creates waves.
Then it's like you got that emotion, you got like a lot of water there too and so it's like
can be a lot of waves at times I think maybe for you. I'm not sure that resonates. Oh there's a
I'm a capricorn, and capricorns kind of like are interesting sign too.
And yeah, I'm a lot of earth and air. I have hardly any water on my chart, except for Scorpio,
or Lillithan Scorpio. You guys, women, we want to check out their Lillith too. Men, especially gay men,
Okay, let's see what we got.
Nathology.
I've got to get you guys in the background while you make your working. So you're popping in and out. Okay, sweetie
Now this book called wisdom of the men. Let me see if there's any wisdom in it. What's reading today?
What is this there's a Hansling little cookbook, what is this?
But I remember they were kind of like hungry turkey and quinoa really come on. What is going on here?
Yeah, I'm just gonna
I'm bad tasting my mouth with the Pokemon. Okay, let's see where we go
It says if it burns you don't succeed
In a picture of a crack day, okay, and it says
Normal sucks, as we called that, is the code of the extraordinary mind. Nordic tales, immortality key, power of awareness, oh, the RAP of the mind.
Ooh, and Madame Clairvonian's Guide to the Stars, that one looks good.
You said, did I, you believe, you think it's going to, I think it's, I don't know, okay.
Yep, that's what I was going to say.
Hmm, this is an interesting book.
chapter one the techniques of individual submission the first part of this book is
devoted to various techniques used to make a meek man a meek conformist in
addition to the actual political occurrences attention is called same
ideas born in the laboratory and the drug techniques that facilitate brain
It says, a fantastic thing is happening to our world.
Today, a man is no longer punished only for the crimes he has, in fact, committed.
Now he may be compelled to confess to crimes that have been conjured up by the judges,
who use his confession for political purposes.
It is not enough for us to damn as evil those who sit in judgment.
We must understand what impels this false admission of guilt.
We must take another look at the human mind and its frailty and vulnerability.
Interesting, huh?
the enforced confession that happened in Korea was, you know, in order to survive, right?
People would, you know.
It says, Scouter-brained simpletons confuse the enemy much more than silent heroes whose stamina was fully undermined in spite of everything.
So it's the right of human reactions under the infernal circumstances,
saw this an ugly truth, the spirit of men can be broken,
men can be reduced to the level of animal behavior,
both torture and victim, finally lose all human dignity.
Ay, ay, ay. Yeah, what's your diastrological signed, um, sac?
The bulbous sac? Oh yeah, so I can look at this Madam Claire Boyant one too,
It's fun, this other book's kind of dark, you know, and boy, too dark a book, but...
How many two jelly donuts? That sounds so good. Yeah, Mr. Big Mice would be so jelly.
I'm having so much jelly. There's nothing to be scared of either, yeah.
There's a he'll be so jealous
Yeah, get in my belly, okay, it's as eagles do not fuck with pigeons. I don't recall that
Nikki sticks has
Let's see shadow and fairy tales. I love fairy tales
The battle for your brain. Okay. Don't know much about mythology. This is good
McDonald's sausage biscuit hash browns bomb
Yep. Okay, so let's see
This is a good book about mythology. Let's see. I
Think it has these questions
these questions like
It says, why was Egypt the gift of the Nile?
Herodotus, who might have been called the world's first travel
writer, coined the phrase, the gift of the Nile
to describe Egypt.
It was a society that has utterly fascinated the Greek tourists
when you visited Egypt back in 450 BC.
Yeah, so Herodotus also said some very far-fetched things.
I don't.
I don't think he's necessarily the most reliable source, but...
Some do believe in him. So there's Egypt.
Here's an Egyptian poem. It's a mythic voice. It's the glorious God came.
On the moon himself, the lord of the two lands, and the guys of her husband, they found her resting in the beautiful palace.
She awoke, and she breathed the perfume of the god, and she laughed at the sight of his naffi, in flame with desire, he hastened toward her.
He lost his heart to the queen.
When he came near to her,
She saw his form as a very God. She rejoiced and explained her beauty.
His love went inside all her limbs. The God's sweet perfumes surfaced through the palace, the perfume of punt, the land of incense.
The greatness of this God did to the woman when he pleased. She kissed him and delighted him with her body.
Wow, pretty sexy.
Okay, so it goes into some Egyptian mythology,
but let's skip it into some Greek mythology,
because Egyptian is very, I think,
a little bit more advanced for just starting, okay.
A little bit more advanced.
You'd like to, oh you like the breakfast burritos? Yeah, I have some breakfast burritos to eat too, but I do.
I'm gonna have this right now. Okay.
It says,
Excelling in the greatness. Excelling in thy greatness.
Live apart in stern seclusion, for the people
heed the man who makes them tremble, mingle not alone among them.
Have no human friend, nor intimate.
Nor favoured in thy train, they serve no goodly purpose.
E'er to sleep, thou lies down, prepared to guard thy life.
A man is friendless at the hour of trial.
I to the needy give, the orphan nourished,
esteemed alike the lowly and the great,
but he who ate my bread made in thorection.
Blended you rise in heaven's light land, O living Aten, creator of life, when you set
up in the western lightland, earth is the darkness as in death.
How many are your deeds, thou hidden from sight, O soul God, beside whom which there
are none?
You made the earth as you wished, you alone.
Okay, in the uh, do you want to hear the myth of Mesopotamia? Do you hear me? Okay, that says
by the rivers of Babylon
and it says
Google a wicked term it says the myths of Mesopotamia
It is an old story, but one that can still be told about a man who loved and lost a friend to death and
Learned he lacked the power to bring him back to life
Gilgamesh reverse narrative
We're not high the heaven had not been named from ground below
Had not been called by name
When sweet and bitter mingled together no read
No read
was plaited, and no rushes muddied the water. The gods were nameless, natureless,
futureless. By the rivers of Babylon, there we sat down. Yeah, we wept when we
remembered Zion. Like other people in the ancient world, the Babylonians
attributed their cultural achievements to the gods who revealed their own lifestyle
to their mythical ancestors. Thus Babylon
itself was supposed to be the image of heaven, and these are the temples of replica of the celestial palace.
Ba-da-ri-ba-za-ba-ba-la-n.
That's all I know. Okay.
In a temple of Babylon, there's a second.
Shrine lower than that in which the sitting figure of Belle all of gold and a golden throne and supported on a base of gold with the golden
Cable sitting beside it. I was told by the Chaldeans that to make all this
More than 22 tons of gold were used outside the temple. It's a golden altar
There's also another one not of gold, but of great size on which full groom sheep are sacrificed on the larger altar
The Chaldeans also offer something like 28 and a half tons of frankincense every year at the festival bell
In the time of Cyrus, there was also the sacred building, a solid gold statue of a man, some 15-feet high.
I had the authority of the Chaldeans, although I never saw it myself, Herodotus.
I never heard of any of these things, but I apparently saw them.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-du
something close. Okay, I'm hungry now. I'm starving. Where's the food?
It's here! It's here!
It's so good
Oh cheers guys
Does that really matter
The hoop oh wow look at this
Yum yum yum
Okay, I gotta try this one first. This is like sparkly
This one's really good. It's like full of cream
This isn't bad. It's really good.
This is pervert. I really like the coffee, too.
Well, that was a week looking for us at 714 714 is a kind of progressive member of 7 double
Here's five nine oh
I thought you were shorter
To the promise I knew this would be too sweet. I mean it's so good. I can't eat all at once
Just sweet
Anywhere under the coffee and then fight
So
Really enjoying like you know, I've had so much fun doing this show and it's like
I hope whatever happens to them the shows doing good the shows
I'm happy to have 16 people in the chat. I'm happy to have I'm happy. However many people have in the chat. I have great people here
real people they're actually
People you guys are really such great supporters and they're here a lot
Thank you guys for always come and hang out with me.
I was like, I never knew people would like my show.
I was like, I had an idea that I would be able to.
I tried to do a kind of a radio show in college with somebody.
It was a disaster.
And I was like, I had no confidence.
I just didn't have, I had no, I just didn't have anything going on back then, right?
Like all I was doing was thinking it was like playing music and stuff like that
And I wasn't very funny
All the love that love the things in life like
All the things will develop
Their own time right
Hi, yeah, I'm six three. Oh, I love you, too
And I'm a very you know
a conventional person, but I do have a good heart.
You need to create your own whack pack, right?
Oh, we have one.
We have SIG.
SIG is in it.
We have Mr. Big Pipes, you know.
We have several wacky people.
We have Noel.
We have, you know, you know, many Manson, maybe.
Not in a good way.
be to me I mean I mean I don't know I think I think we're all we're all a little bit
yeah well I wouldn't say what it's like that's not a whack pack it's like more of like a
it's like the well-known character but it's like not you know the whack pack was kind of the mean
thing this is not like the same thing it's like more like the standout people in the
Think I was just thinking like the people that go up on the panels and stuff like that
other kind of the people that are like
The people stand out in chat, but it's like you really know
Once you start going on panel, you really get noticed. So if you're interested in like, you know
Getting more in the spotlight. I used to not want to be
Now I can't get the fuck out of it
Yeah, ban from Benny's Wow, why?
Food ban, do you know?
Is that pie?
Okay, what do we have here?
A good witch.
There's a lot of books on basecraft.
Bible.
name is Johnny. He thinks you're a black guy. Who are you shy? I have a feeling shy is like shy.
Are you like just joking or something? I don't know. I love it's very funny. Okay.
It's how to grow your own cult. This can be that teach you guys. Let me see
After that, they got no can accuse me of starting a cult because I'm teaching how to
Starting a cult. Okay
You're not joking. Okay. Well, this looks good. I mean, it looks looks pretty the cult reports
You could use the Colbert report
Let's see what it says. It says, oh, hello. It says
Most people think that they just need one magic ad that generates leads or sales and works for them for a lot
At least longer than a few weeks
Well, I don't know if this is a real cult. It's a marketing scam. That's what cults are
Colts get a bad rap
This one has no spaceship no compound in Central America no poison Kool-Aid and we don't want all your money
You will leave your friends behind when your business explodes
Here's the best part. You're already in a cult. You just don't know it
Terrifying thought
Okay
What is it showing? It makes some sense. So it's showing things too. Oh, it's the conversation between
Okay, I don't know if the culture scary not really that scary
What are you talking? I mean, it's like while you're talking a lot you got banning from bennie things your black man
His name is John. Yeah, I'm the female at joking. No, it's actually not funny culture. Yeah. Well, it's so is
The amount of words you've just written, right? I mean, it's like a whole
whole column
Have you done anything with the people in chat?
Sack, it doesn't matter, I'm kind of,
oh, it's okay if you're kind of chubby.
What are you doing?
You're sitting on top of the donuts.
I keep thinking you're talking about the sask,
but you're talking about the bull to sack.
And the difference between sask and bull to sack.
And you know what the difference is?
10 square inches of ball skin.
I'm sorry, nevermind.
That was not funny.
Hold on.
Ah.
Okay.
Um.
Ah.
To buy a vagina
A vagina
I don't know
I'm just making songs up, oh my gosh, online, oh my gosh
I forgot I was on TV
Okay
Let's see, there's the, yeah
mysterious secret societies, initiate magic.
I mean, there's so many billion books,
I have a million books.
A wizard's guide to defensive baking.
Animal folk tales, it's your best physical feature.
Boss vibes, angel guidance, creativity,
take back your life.
Fire dancer straight bullets
Wow
What Benny was talking about giving up yesterday on live and crying everyone was trying to be support
I don't know what how he's doing today. Well, I mean he sounds like he's not doing too. Well, I mean you should be your band already. I mean
You're making it worse
Rebombing Benny out
Really it's hard to get a band there really is
Um
Uh, there's a couple jelly doing it I got two jelly doing it's two jelly two jetties
I got two jetties. Do you want do you want a jelly easy? I got you a jelly donut. If you like come get one
Yeah
You want to see the jelly i'll get in a little bit
I still have to eat the rest of my
Uh, are you trying to help Benny? I know. I know. We all, we all want to help Benny, but I don't know.
Some, some, some things are a big task. Of course, it would require a village, you know?
Yeah. Okay.
So, what have we got here?
Yeah, I mean, I don't have the comic books of the of her, I mean, I have I just have
Catwoman and for out again.
Okay, not really.
Here's a guide to the stars.
Let's read about Scorpio and other such beautiful things.
Okay, let's start with Capricorn. Let me give you more. It's Capricorn the Intellectual.
A long time ago, at a very loud party in a probably haunted house in New Orleans,
while music dumped in the living room, I sat on the back porch steps talking
to a woman about astrology. She was a Capricorn and wanted to know
what I could tell her about herself. She wanted to know what I could tell her about herself.
When I told her Capricor was typically understood to be the sign of the discipline and boundaries,
She looked theatrically behind us into the house, where the empty beer cans overflowed from the kitchen trash can, where all the furniture smelled like wet dogs, where a bad romance was currently dramatically coming to an end.
This was the house where food scraps were being dropped and then bent so chaotically through the house that the next morning my roommate and I would just find pretzel crumbs.
ground into the floors and couches, but the windowsills,
the inside of the fridge and the grout
between the bedroom tiles.
If I'm supposed to be grown up, this woman's face said,
then tell me what I'm doing here.
Two possible meanings, two possible feelings.
They quail up inside that expression.
The last for the first possibility was that she saw some truth in that description of her sign and was expressing in an ironic dismay
Or the distance in maturity of her soul and the juveniles self-indulgent squalor she found herself currently in
You've seen a guy and watching YouTube. Oh good
You know depression when you see it something maybe bitten bitting to go outside more. Well
Maybe he is kind of pent up in that little house, you know, hi babe
That's so good
It's Boba sack your boyfriend cat lover
What's going on with you in Bulbasack?
Nosey
He dumped you on tiktok. Did you do a tiktok dance? That's humiliating. I'm sorry about that
Do you dance? Do you do like a breakup dance?
Do you do it in front of all his followers that's embarrassing
I'm sorry
Biggie
Oh
Oh, my chick see baby my chick see oh
Well, I suppose there's worse ways to be dumb can be like literally
Don't don't
I love some feedback on the graphics guys, I love some suggestions, I love some feedback.
A little bit quiet, I love some, you know, if you share the show, if you'd like to let
friends know.
I'm still around, I'm sorry that I haven't been consistent or my quality is not consistent.
Have a great show and you know continue to keep you guys entertained and
Long time to come so I love you guys so much. All right
Hmm
Yes, I have two and I have two of these two okay, I thought we really met Capricorn, right?
So the astrology, okay, so maybe the world's opportunities.
Let's return to the very basic building blocks
of Capricorn, the symbol, the element,
is quality, the ruling planet.
So it's Capricorn's constellation is the goat.
Traditionally, it's been associated
with the mythic sea goat, a creature with the head
of a head and body of a goat, the tail of a fish,
but it's a contemporary iconography.
It's most often displayed as a mountain goat
galing a craggy peak.
Like his cousin's Taurus and Virgo, Capricorn is an earth sign, and this earth sign energy
is most alive not in dreams or emotions, or the abstract workings of the mind, but in
the realm of physical material reality.
This can mean caring about one's physical surroundings, and earth sign is most likely
to care about choosing the right color to paint the walls, or the least likely to be
people's things. This isn't about fussiness necessarily, it's more the sign of a person who notices the physical world very deeply,
who lives on the material plane full-time.
And for this cardinal sign, the signs that mark the sort of a season and the
and that embodying energy of initiative and forward motion,
its Earth sign energy focuses not only on the realities
of here and now,
but on the moving toward a concrete material future.
This is a sign most comfortable working
toward long-term goals,
most comfortable with advancement over time,
most comfortable choosing a point in the horizon
and moving toward it with unwavering certainty.
When is Capricorn's ruling planet of Saturn that imbues it with so much of its aura of authority and control?
Saturn is the planet of discipline and intimidation
Our limitations of authority and rules of influence can be a fiercest and challenging one
If the moon bears the energy of the archetypal mother, nursery and soft
Saturn is the opposite, the archetypal father, distant, demanding, strict.
Traditionally, Saturn is one of the so-called malefic planets.
Along with Mars, there are planets of problems with difficulties.
Even bad omens, the planets traditionally mark points of trouble or a warning on an astrological chart.
Capricorn is motivated by the dream of advancement and recognition.
It's energy is too focused too serious to bother doing something that isn't a goal in mind
If Capricorn is going to try to do thing at all they're going to try to do it
Well to try to do the best and be recognized as the best
Makes perfect sense that this would be interpreted to mean that Capricorn is a sign of career goals
There's also space to interpret it more widely might be more accurate to think of Saturn as a planet that represents the work
You choose to do in this world whether or not that work relates to business
Whether or not that work is prepared, Capricorn isn't willing to labor for no reward at all,
but that doesn't mean that the reward has to be money.
Capricorn is after all the sign of the earth associated with the sea goat and the mountain
god, but also sometimes with a god pan, half goat, half man, impudent and lusty and closely
connected to the earth.
Pleasures of existence.
In personal relationships, Capricorns, Discipline, Emotional, Rigor can be happy, burdened publicly. However, Capricorns, Discipline can be a strong sense of responsibility to the world.
And this is Aquarius, it's the weirdo, so you gotta check out this book, I'll read it to you too if you want to see it, but Aquarius, the weirdo.
It's a rare condition, this day and age, to read any good news on the newspaper page.
Love and tradition of the grand design, some people say it's even harder to find.
Well then there must be some magic clue inside these gentle walls.
With all I see, it's a power of dreams
We love birds that we have received
And things go by
It's a rare condition this day and age.
It's a rare condition this day and age
Well then there must be some magic you know some I think I think full house
Let days go by
It's the bigger love of the family
You bet, so
Joe and I can do a do a do out of that
Sorry, my apologies. Here I come
Hello guys, yeah, so I had to order this new
Like look at see look at this is the
See this this is like supposed to be
Like this goes on that but like it's me hardly stays on there
I think it used to screw on there doesn't even screw on there. It's like it's like weren't down
Oh, that's the wrong one.
Oh, shit.
Oh, excuse me.
Okay, that works.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, it's a kind of,
I mean, that was to kind of make a more innocent time.
In the country, you know, and it's like when we like kind of like that's all we had to watch too, right?
And so everyone was watching the same thing at the same time
Now we're now everybody's watching on their own time
You know watching the whole season of the shows in a day and stuff like that. It's just crazy
So now now it took a lot to but used to be very you know, we'd all watch this
Everyone watched the same thing at the same time. We all talk about it the next day
Did you see all can you believe that this happened this happened it's like now, but then it's a kind of just different right because we don't really do that you know
It's a recognition
Sorry
I'm trying to myself crazy doing this
Some people say
The Trump Trumpa Trumpa
Okay.
As days go by.
If anyone would like a reading, I got readings available right now.
Also, if you'd like to do like an hour reading, I'll do $25 for an hour on the phone.
You'd like to really detailed one. Yeah, but you have to schedule that ahead of time. I'm probably on through discord
You'd like to do that
Special only only available to you guys here
Okay, what else do I got I wouldn't say that beta it's not a coke for 48 hours. Oh my god
Um, so, have you heard of the stream, only JS?
Only JS?
What is that?
Dr. Zaeus, Dr. Zaeus, only J-U-S? I don't know. I don't know if I heard of them.
Let's see what it's about.
Linked accounts, God. I want to, okay, I can collect, God, okay.
At least, okay, this is cool. I can get in.
Amazon is really cool. You can play all those steam games, or not steam, but you can play the ones on Gogg.
Just another platform.
as American.
Mm-hmm. I'm sorry guys
Zoning out trying to get on me. Oh, it's like I'm getting my
Oh, we got someone on hello
Oh, we got here
My friend you hear me good morning. Yes, sir I can
Hi, how are you today? Oh?
Living a dream, man. I'm still working on yesterday. I got a little bit of time left look like you could do somebody to interact with so I just like
Yeah, I was kind of most passing out. I'm trying to log into Gog. Have you heard of Gog? Gog is like a
Yeah, that's DRM free games and Gog is the best site to purchase games from if you're gonna do them digitally
It's not quite as convenient or easy as
Steam or
epic. Yeah, but yeah, it's better for long term.
So it's always just like, I just figured out you can like, on
Amazon's, with their Luna system, whatever, it can hook into
the Gog and like a lot of others, like Ubisoft, and like, they
can play those games actually from like Amazon, like you're
without having to like,
I don't log into the other site. I just figured it out. So I was trying to log in there
So who is this guy? This is Drumpal stills game. Drumpal stills has been on the show before. Oh, I
Think he's oh my doughnuts just I got some doughnuts. It's good. Good morning chat. I am I am lurking
I'm in the chat. I just didn't simply hang on
Yeah, I've been going did you have a nice 4th of July and I'm going on with you
Live in the dream more than I want to talk about on a public setting. Okay. I'm sorry, you know just for just for reference
Yeah, I'm always living a dream. That was good. I mean
We're right end up that's where I'm supposed to be right. Oh, yeah
Yes, exactly like
Well, you know, we hope so, you know, that's that. Oh, yeah, I would hope so also otherwise
Well, I think if you're not where you're supposed to be, you know, where are you?
Where are you and why, you know, so, Chad, just, we're just two guys sitting in the
hot tub four feet apart, okay?
There's nothing else to it, we're just hanging out.
Or be a part in the hot tub, you know, you don't know what's going on under the surface of the hot tub
I could be giving him a hand job or you know rubbing his feet
You know, you don't you never know but I'm four feet apart. Are you mr. Elastic or mr. Fantastic or Elastic fantastic?
I don't remember a little bit apart. I mean, I think you're a four elastic girl four feet from my
My feet I don't know. Okay, so so maybe they should just grind on each other
It's just oh, yeah, we should grind that's why it's called grinder because we end up right no
I think mr. Mr. Mr. Rumpelstiltskin is very straight. He's he's grumpy. He's now he's
He's not smiling when he hears these jokes. He's
oh no i'm smiling on the inside however i'm incredibly straight like i'm violently straight
yes yes yes the biology yes i can hang it he's not getting out he's about to get chosen i can't
hang out i know i know yeah you're you're all hate crime in me right now this is super weird
well yeah that's why there are hate crimes people like you you know you protect protect me you know
now it's okay i'm just kidding i'm sure you're very hey mojo joe yeah i mean i know people are
How people treat gay people is that it was always very oh, you know
Oh, there was always very accepting outwardly
For the most part, but then it was like a lot of stuff behind the back. It's like a that's what I always found like
There's always like, you know, it's always like some kind of okay. Let's fly you right there. Bye. You're right there
Mojojo, how's a cat lover shy?
I know people need to be nice to the gays.
Yeah, exactly, you're gonna go to jail if you don't.
That's when there's hate crimes.
Nice and black people too.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
I'm just, you know, yeah.
What's in your hand, is that a fountain pen?
It is a, it's the,
little clicky pen oh not a fountain pen okay um it is a screw you writing your own name on
a styrofoam dumpies did i i didn't write it but i can't don't no just this just uh this
kind of dead but i do um i have been drawing pictures of people in this chat oh so uh oh
Um, let's see cat lover some of my okay, so we're having some good conversations in the chat. You can draw this guy if you want
Yeah, I mean he's I
Think the last couple times of I've been on your stream to hang out. I got called out for being
Straight like it was like hey, that's that's that's not welcome here kind of stuff
But like no, oh, please. Oh, it's not welcome here. I know most people okay
No, it wasn't you it was just kind of
You know the vibe well, I don't I don't know if there are any other gay people here besides like 40 diamond
and like I don't know maybe a couple other people but
Yeah, you can my parents were straight, you know, so, you know, I accept straight people. I know
I have all straight brothers and sisters
Parents are straight. My parents were straight. Yeah, they're both had restriction. They're a Mary
You know, they're actually married the opposite sex, which you know
I'm believable this day and age, but yeah, they're actually straight and who's even straight anymore. It's like minority these days
Everybody's got to have something like
Yeah, well
You know, I guess people will always be the majority though
That's a majority that it's like it's such a laugh and they're like, oh, they're threatened by gate
Like it gave people a 10% like less than 10% of the population
What kind of danger are less than 10% yeah, yeah, and do you think do you think I was gonna be seduced by a
You know straight men are always letting me start being seduced by gay men. Well, some of them. Well, that's kind of
In some cultures they frown upon unbearded men because they say it makes the dudes look like women and that's gonna tempt
the men to be gay
That's an interesting take, isn't it? That's like the part of the culture, though. I won't say which countries
Well, I know I'm seeing it. I think it's in Arabic, in Arabic, but but I'm thinking yeah, you're correct
that's and
Also, the bearded stuff is like yeah, it's like so it's like, you know, they're gonna be like, you know
Not growing beers at a time, right or like the twinkish or whatever
Yeah, it's interesting. There's like also interesting stuff about these botchi boys or something like that
I don't know. They have these warlords, the Afghanistan warlords. They have apparently these dancers and stuff like that
I don't know. It's very strange cultural
Different things in different countries, right? There's a lot of different stuff and what you're used to that goes on in, you know, Arab world
Yeah
Um, yeah, I've heard this we've heard this story, but you know, no no shade on new religion
I don't I don't I didn't study that extensively to be able to
You know debate or anything, so
I'll just say living that live, right? That's my my motto. Oh, no, they don't really so much
Oh, yeah, well, they don't I I mean, I do I do that that's what I do
But they don't know they they say, you know, they live in like, um, you know, there's a
Line up against the wall and knock the wall over.
Do you know the word defenestration?
What does that mean? Give me a great definition.
It's a very specific term. It means to throw somebody out of a window.
Okay. That happened to the guy that, like, you know...
They do that to the acid on the guy that yeah, they do that to
Some of those oh, yeah, throw out the window or
Yeah
Yeah, I mean
Yeah, well, it's not not not fun for them obviously, but I mean just that that that specific of a term
has a specific word for it. I think that's fun, just linguistically it's fun.
It's not fun to get tossed out of a window.
No, no, that's not. Just let the language be stressed.
The noun and the noun being used on. Yeah, exactly.
They used to have a bearded lady in the circus.
The circus, yeah.
Yeah, exactly. Well, whatever, whatever
Definis straight. Yeah, they used to the verb if in a straight thing
You know vanilla ice was almost been a straightened by a
So night wasn't it how they used to have bearded lady to the circus back in the day?
Yeah, well, these are just women with the you know
with the
Overactive lands. Yeah
Yeah, or yeah
you know yeah or whatever or just actually men that were like saying they're women
Hey, these old circus freak shows were crazy. Yeah, those p.t. Barnum
But Barnum also said there's a sucker born every minute, so you don't even know how many of these these
You know exhibits were actually even authentic a lot of them. We're just you know flim flam and
When playing Sam they called him. Yeah
But he was brilliant because you can read what was his PT Barnum wrote, you know, a very famous book, you know.
There might have been cruelty involved in it, but it did make elephants to small-town USA so people could see them in real life.
Okay.
Well, it's like it kind of reminds me a little bit of Howard Sturm, where Howard Sturm will have people that are like, you know, maybe like men to the different levels or different, you know, different physical things going on.
He will.
Showcase them, you know, he didn't like promote music dwarf tossing, which is unfortunate, but you know, did
PT bar them to the same thing where it's like these were people that were kind of like shunned by their community and they were like stuck in their house and they were
basically, you know, dependent on the state and then all of a sudden they had a
city income they had a you know some fame they had
Thought all of a sudden they're getting married having kids
So they had kind of a normal life after that and so a lot of them did so I think beetle juice came to fame not not not
Michael Keaton or that you know the make a Tim Burton movie, but the black door
Yeah, with the really jack-of-teeth. Yeah, he was his stage name at least as beadlejuice
I don't know if that was a real name, but he got notoriety from that and like hey
Yeah, I want to see things that he does
Yeah, well he was actually the one that he was that you know
He started at the dwarf tossing and came in with another dwarf to the Howard Stern
they promoted the dwarf tossing then Howard kind of fell in love with you know him specifically and
and then he was able to kind of parlay into just doing the appearances without doing the
being tossed, you know, and there's like a bunch of pulling pins like he was.
It feels like a net positive for him.
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like that he was a bubble boy. He was like, you know, a huge star. I mean,
he's not even a huge star. I mean, it's like a celebrity. He was one of the most popular whack
packers, right? But he is, you know, now he's 58 years old. I think that's a long time for people
Yeah, quick question. So, so Lady Gaga is big in gay music culture, like gay club scene culture, right?
Like Lady Gaga is big, right?
Mm-hmm. I think it's popular.
I, it was, I don't remember. It wasn't when it happened, but I came to respect Lady Gaga as a
creator, performer, musician when I saw the clip of
Her performing and how her stern where yeah, she was still wearing the like the thong costume and like the stage clothes
but it was just her and a piano and
Singing and doing the song like a couple of her songs and yeah, oh wait not only she can play she got pipes
She got actual pipes, too
Okay, I'm in like that that got me over the threshold of like, ah the like meme whatever
Yeah, it's fine
things be the next Madonna, you know whatever but
Oh
Okay, now now I'm in like so respect to Lady Gaga and that is that was um, that was my moment for
Hey, well, yeah, it's really gay thing. I mean, I'm I also respect it
All right, we could
Mean I mean, I think she's a straight woman. I mean, I'm not
But, uh, Athena, yeah, like Lisa Jordana is the same thing. She plays the piano, so you would think, oh, she's, you know, she's not like, you know, she's not a real musician or whatever, but she is, and she'll play the piano acapella, and then she'll play the piano and sing along with it, her own music and stuff, and so people that can perform.
instrument, you know, it's definitely Mr. Big Pipes. No, you don't count Mr. Big Pipes.
Oh, a lot of the stuff that ends up in like club music is very processed and produced.
But if you can take just one person doing one instrument, I mean, piano is a little cheating because it's like, got the entire range, but one person, one instrument and then also singing, I, dude, I, I play an instrument.
at least a few times a month gigs
But I don't sing at the same time like I'm not a singer
But I do karaoke and like I can't sing and play at the same time
And I'm not all that good of a singer, but it's fun. You know, it's fun time
Yeah, I like to I can't play her
Really an instrument. I took piano for a long time, but
I can't play but I do like to I do have I can carry a tune a little bit and I like to sing
In a bucket if I have a bucket nice
There don't drop it
That's looking good which without getting into
Self-promotion way too much. I just did a karaoke night. I think I'm gonna do it once a month. I've done a few of them
Okay, it's just just like being you know at a bar. Hey bring a song and then you present the song just so you're in sync with it and then
Yeah
And you should be able that you should have no problem. You know, it's not on YouTube, right? Yeah, you're on YouTube doing this
Well, I'm on I went I'm not live right now. I stream on YouTube twitch cake. Oh, where do you do the karaoke nights?
Where do you do the karaoke night?
I use OBS Studio and I'm going back and like I'm trying to figure out how to get because I can all of my chat is linked
But not everybody, if anybody else wants to go live in StreamYard, that's not linked to, they're not linked to each other, I'm working on figuring that piece out.
I think if you go to your settings, go through all the settings and make sure that there should be a setting that says allow the other StreamYard people to...
That's if you're live on StreamYard, but I'm...
Live with OBS Studio sending out to multiple. Okay. Mmm. Those are linked via like I just it's turnkey solution
Restream.io and that has a cross chat bot that links all the chats, which the
If you just if everybody's like just live by a stream yard
They can't see each other's chats, but the streamer can't that all the streamers everybody who's in the call can see
I'm working on a I'm trying to work on. Hey, how do they all see each other's?
Like why does that happen? Yeah, I mean, I mean, yeah, that does because they're being able to put just makes community better
Yeah, oh, yeah, I
Started streaming on kick recently too. I mean, I haven't got really many people from it, but oh
Where you at?
Look at the link in the back shatter link in your in your chat. No. Oh, yeah
I'm trying to watch this on YouTube right now.
Yeah, I have about 100 memberships on YouTube
now, which is pretty cool.
Also had some interesting, a clapping system
that's been pretty lucrative, pretty successful,
have some controversial people on the show and it's always like what you can pay $25 if you'd
like to have someone kicked off the show for 24 hours and then you know and some people have
and then we try different methods of the system and one of them involved like you know
That person's able to untie themselves out with the same amount of money and there's not a refund
And then you you can like retail them out and then they can return they can time. Yeah
Mr. Psych you don't you don't do much in the in the quote panel verse. Do you that's like
Barely, no, there's like
Like usually like kind of a menu of stuff that you can do like paying. Oh, hey, here's tips
That can pay money to change somebody's name in a stream yard call. That's the thing you can do
Yeah, we have to get put in the back in the background for x amount of time and that x equals how many dollars it is
that type of thing, there's all kinds of stuff.
There's a lot of menu options that are.
Yeah, I mean, and I've seen that,
but it's like a kind of different on YouTube
where it's like people are just basically interested
in getting people kicked off.
And there's people that have the animosity,
there's like really controversial people.
And so it's basically, I figured out a way to monetize,
monetize something negative.
That's like, it's kind of an alchemy.
And so it's like, that's kind of a boom.
Yeah, and it's I've had a lot of people timed up for 24 hours. What a stupid thing to waste your money out
Yeah, but if people people spending their money out and it's like they had they get actually a chance to produce the show
They get a chance to be on the show without you having somebody else on the show. You're thinking the same thing
Well, people spend their money on different things and money system energy
And it's a way to monetize your stream to make it more worthwhile for the time that you put into it as a creator
Right and people
Are great for everybody
Some of those things if you host panels some of those things are probably gonna be good for you to do
Yeah, I mean the people seem to hate you won't say it will tell me if you if you care
But I mean yeah, people seem to hate on people that are just making money like they're like, oh my god
You think it's the guy the other day like this guy Q45 was like, oh my god
He was making money like he thinks you just make money just sitting there, you know on on stream
Well, that's what I mean. What do you think a radio person that does a radio show does and he doesn't like almost the same thing
He does the same thing. He's the same kind of system to my his show
Just like mine was more popular or something. I don't know. He's mad. It's asinine
It's an asinine take because I mean if you're hosting the if you're hosting the show
It's your house rules if people want to participate in that then you're subject to whatever the house rules are
If you don't want to participate in that you're
Welcome to not participate in that
yeah and people oh thank you mojo joe like mojo joe has been a member for one
month thank you so much yeah people always find a reason to complain about
something but so I just have to ignore you know it's people always like haters
hate yeah exactly and it's like oh I'm I met people always go oh
Well, you're not even a streamer like I like well, I think I kind of in this I mean I do it basically pulled
You know from the moment I wake up to the fall to sleep. I'm pretty much streaming like I'm
Who said you're not a streamer? Oh
several people have several people have
Let's say
I think you go live more than me. Yeah, I go live every day. I've got my every day. Let's hear except one day
I'm almost like a hundred members. Yeah, that's that's just haters hating then because you're obviously a
You're a content creator and you're obviously a streamer. Yeah, like oh my every day
Like oh, it's a you like it's a hobby for you're like it's a hobbyist a hobby
They're like you're they think they know how much I mean, it's like people just like lines of hobby
Yeah, well, it's like a lot of people I'm having as a hobby and it's like sometimes the hobby is
Makes money too. It's like, you know, and they can but I'm saying I also have a registered LLC for my yeah, you know
Because I yeah hard
Yeah, yeah, you think it'll be very seriously right and so it's and so people yeah coltings hobbies and things
You know that the the success in life is being able to get paid to do what you love
I think it's like, you know, it's like that so it's like I didn't feel like work
You're doing doing just there's living your life and you're being paid like that's pretty much
But so people will get angry if they
Aren't able to do that but everyone can do that like the truth is you can but it's like it's not
That's the easiest thing. Well
would disagree and say no not everybody can because some people are literally
boring bitches that can't hold attention for anything and and then the
counterpoint of that is if just hard recommend if you're doing something that
you can double dip and stream while you're doing it
That way you're making money and then streaming it and then making money from streaming it and double-dib that way and then
Having the static content videos where like there's ad revenue
Triple did triple dipping on just something that you're doing you're putting your time in and now you're monetizing it three different ways
That's just smart. That's just yeah
And when you once your mom says on YouTube you get to do that because you can have a membership
You can have the super chats and you can have the ad revenue up a bit. Of course. I made one for me
Yeah, yeah anywhere else. Yeah, it's on YouTube. Right. I didn't know you come up
Welcome in exiled one. What's we get to be it's just shimmy yard. Yeah. Good morning. Yeah. Good morning
Streamer brah. He'd be over there on some of the sectors I'd be in
I like to stick to the content without all the fuckery and he joins in on this
Standardized trolling instead of going personal. It is pretty good streamer psyche. I don't know if you've met him before
Yeah, he's been on the show a few times. Yeah, and
He's I like him a lot better than mr. Big Pipes and
And some other people I don't know if you know mr. Big Pipes. He's terrible, but uh
You've met before but don't remember okay. He plays like a harmonica around. He's like a one-man band kind of thing
But uh, oh, that's fun
Yeah, he's a little bit. He's a little bit
Okay, so shorts and videos that require editing and the whatnot will make more money. Yeah, but I need an editor
I can't do all that work. I mean, it's like there's a lot I'd like not not have thousands of hours of
I have hundreds of videos so now it's like gonna be impossible to do all the editing like I mean it's like so I mean
I have to be I'd be working
I have a full of fucking years of work just doing the editing of my videos right if I just did the editing on the videos
I have right now
The years of food right or years of work just to get the short short amount of footage out
so
Extremely successful channels hardly had the drama drama gets views, but it doesn't sell that makes sense
Well, yeah, it's I've seen like the hundred people in the chat and then nobody's
participating or doing anything or they're donating and then I have like, you know a
Few people in the chat and everyone's doing it. So it's the good. Yeah, the quantity over
quality over quantity, right?
What happened to the pipes guy abandoned from the show? But he's around sometimes.
I appreciate the kind words about how I how I interact it is a hundred percent
garbage in is garbage out I I'm not like I'm not saying match energy but if
if somebody lags themselves that I mean sometimes I have to escalate and then I have to troll
if I'm having a good conversation and like we're talking about things I can weave memes in and
That's that's just like we're just hanging out right now if somebody were to come in and start like you know start doing personal insults
Then or or something that just like
Walk okay. Yeah, that will not triggers me, but is just
Yeah, I have to troll that person and that that's like it's a personal flaw and I realize that but we're just hanging out right now
I'm like
Some of us function off of energy, you know I'm saying we're conductors whatever energy you give me
I'm gonna give back. I like to refer to myself
And trolling can also be like a defense mechanism.
It can also be a bonding mechanism too sometimes.
You know, it can be like a hazing kind of thing.
I mean, it has a lot of functions and functions in there.
I can write a whole book about trolling.
I plan to undoing it actually on all the,
okay, all the has to, all the encompasses a lot.
JT go up.
Yeah, JT is welcome up, yeah.
Yes, I mean, yes, I'd like to
Not tonight, but not tonight, but some at some time. Yeah, because I think I'm writing a book
I used to say I use troll techniques for for the power of good, but now at this point. I don't even know
Right. Well, I mean
Yeah, you got lost in this house. I
Troll not for the pat not really good
You know, it's like a first troll of trolls or whatever like, you know, but I'm talking about like there's some trolling that is fun
Like, you know, I don't know if you heard of miss Netta
Joe Netta is like a
really interesting Alabama drag queen that probably, you know, probably 15,000
Oh, no, I don't know subscribe
Yeah, but probably at least a thousand people in their chat all the time, but the chat is that's 100% trolls
I mean she looks like Bill Cosby and like, you know, and she's like six foot five and she I mean it's very interesting
And she's the she's just but it's like so much fun to troll
It's like one of the funnest chat rooms if you were go to like miss net at the real mrs. Net and Charles
she's in her trailer making like really really terrible food and
It's really entertaining
You know, you hear about like watch like watching bad, you know, the bad cooks and stuff. It's just
Hey psyche, I watch this old lady named Cynthia carvers. Oh black lady issue. You get a super ghetto gangster
bro
Oh
It's just being a whole I just make sure there's the real beat
It's media. Oh my god, media is on the phone. I do not like my name mentioned. Okay. Oh, good morning
I don't like I don't like I don't like I don't like I don't like
You know
You don't meet his puppies meet his puppies. Are you me this puppy? I don't know who it's me top puppy is
It's you
Who is this guy the man there next to you?
Martin intelligent young and then
He thinks like he analyzed the
And then the high side over there with the high stinky is with the high stinky.
Here's I'm not I'm not smart. No, I'm a simple monkey
Analyze the reason why
Fingers and toes you think you think you think you think you're bad like
Don't come like that. I just I'm just being a nice
The reason why you came up here because you think I'm not good at analyze. No, I didn't come here for you
I came here for psyche
You're not significant. You're not a pie in my life.
Well, this ain't a pie symbol.
I don't eat slices of pie like you.
You're very not good for my health.
You're a symbol. This is...
Saki.
Yes.
I love you. I came from Croatia.
Croatia? I thought you were from...
Croatia?
Who she has to she sounds very much? Oh, no. Oh, that was German. Oh
Wait, hang on. It's Croatian like really something
I think it is an Eastern Europe
Breckenzee, I don't know
They speak too many languages for me tougher. I don't know
Are they trolling me? I can barely speak. Are they trolling me?
No, you're calling yourself right now. I
Just speak a lot of languages that like toddler level
Yeah
I just think it's a different language.
I think it's cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
You're too much.
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool,
cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
I got my password right there.
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
Don't say that. That was very racist of you. Don't say cuckoo or chew again. It's a racist thing in a different language
How do you make it more racist though?
Really bad word in my country
It doesn't
No, it's it's racist. It's like
Machu
well
It's towards educate us. I don't know. I don't know. We don't speak your language
Which is you at the real beat me that where's the real meter?
I don't know what meter is good kids fucking fucking bitch you fucking asshole. I'm gonna porn bomb you now
Whatever
You're so good with the poor bombing tactic use. Thank you
You tell me everything. You tell me how to how to combat it. Yes
You're you you're your crow crow crow at right?
She's Persian M your crow magnet
No, no, not crow magnet. You said you were from Croatia. No, I am from
Kokila Stupala Imash.
Oh, Shishpashu tipi shida Tudushees.
Tudushees.
That was so many words.
I didn't know you speak Croatian.
I don't. I looked that up on a channel.
Oh, very good. Very good. I like that.
What do you think I said?
I like the Koreshianis that you do.
What do you think I said, though?
I like Koreshia.
My parents are from Koreshia.
I tried to learn hard the Koreshia language,
but I understood what you said and I like it.
So how many is it?
How many languages do you speak?
You speak three languages.
I asked the question in Croatian.
Hang on.
Did you not understand what I...
Saki, what is this guy talking?
Please translate.
I don't speak Croatian.
I have no idea.
I don't speak English.
Can you ask a question?
I don't speak Croatian.
I have no idea.
What does that mean? What does that mean, what does that mean, Mida?
I, yeah, what does that mean? Are you talking about me in Croatia?
No, no, it's just, it's a great, it's a funsy question.
Oh. He's being very rude.
Yes, no, no, I just
Not I said how many how many feet do you have?
Just being very racist because I only have four feet and he's been very racist to my my feet
here, I
German a little bit earlier or something very close to German and
Croatian doesn't look like I don't speak English, okay?
Cuckoo machu. Oh, I don't know what you're saying. I don't
Dottie come get your girl, bro. Don't get your girl
Yeah, are you getting god in Amida? I'm dating this motherfucking gay guy named fucking soccer
Psycho from Koreshio. Oh, Psycho from Koreshio? Oh, Psychi from Koreshia.
Right. The funny thing about Croatia. Psycho from Koreshio. If you look at a map...
The funniest thing about Croatia is it looks like Bosnia was like,
hey, we're going to go to the beach and Croatia is like that again.
You didn't even let me finish.
I don't care about your intellectual conversation.
I don't care how intelligent.
Talk about what you are.
No, I'm a little money
I'm me I wasn't being rude to you
Said it wasn't your country either, but I wasn't being I live now in the United States
No, good, then you won't be mad when the United States turns your country into
Russian the side corner fucking pie go away
I just I just looked up how to say the thing that I wanted to ask you that
Yeah
Was really good though, so I mean bonus points for example
That's okay
Yes, very good. How do you know your accent is good though, but I didn't know I didn't know I cheat because she said it was
That's okay. Well, she's he doesn't know Chloe. He doesn't think she knows Croatian. Yeah, and I'll speak Croatian
Who the fuck is beta?
Yo, I'm me talk. Oh, you're there is no me. I'm gonna beat your meter
I mean, I'm meeting your beta. I'm gonna nickname you. I'm from Croatia. I no longer from Iran. I came from Croatia
Are you a Croatian spy pretending to be Iranian princess? Yes. I knew it
Fuck you. But she's really a transsexual
Well, we've gotten to the bottom of a lot of things this is today
Where are you holding me
the
Um, I think it's a your small to your large what what is the content of the
What would you what is his channel like what would what did you do? I think he like on this karaoke and stuff
One once a month ish now, uh, that's kind of where I'm at and you do what you do
otherwise usually I talk on your show or
I do my own. So I won an award for the best garage
you do on Twitch for 2019 and 2020. I think it's like a
very good thing where people live vicariously through seeing
somebody else get something. I know I know I know many
people like that. I do a lot of panels. Pretty good. It's good
for different groups. No, I can tell you I know every day
I'm trying to talk. I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I'm trying to talk, I
Just keep those Bosnians away from the beach. That's what Croatia does
I bought you a plane ticket. I don't like it.
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
OK, I don't like any of this.
This guy on the right, that's called like, I don't know,
like Paposhi, I don't know.
When the guy is a pie, it's a simple pie.
Or it's like it's like also, hey, or what else?
What is that, Chet or something? Is that Chet?
What is the exile?
I don't know that symbol on the bottom right, that's that's pie.
Yes, hi, but it's also. Hey, it's Hebrew, too
But anyway
Hear me complaining about you eating the neighbor's pets. Yeah, yeah, exactly
What about the tations I think would you save on pet?
You're not passing Koresh. Yeah, I don't know what he's talking about.
Hold on. We eat them every day.
Yeah. What else?
I would have to beat.
I thought she was going to sleep.
Who is this mother fucker?
Good morning.
I don't know you fucker.
Be the header coffee today.
I am not it.
It's okay.
It's Mita.
Uncle Koresh.
OK.
My bad, I'm sorry, I shut the fuck up. I don't know who you are go back to your fucking country
Okay, that's kind of rude
Stompila you must
Okay, Stopeila
What's five times three is Stopeila Imash Stokeila. I want a nice little kilo
Four so Paul still Paula image
That's a Croatian for how many feet do you have? Wow? We do not speak like that sounds like super
Like a new
You're retarded in my language. Yeah
No, I know
She's talking about herself
No, I'm talking about you
The right to you. Yeah, Bita. Did you change your accent everything?
Sorry
I really thought people was the only one I was gonna have to deal with with multiple personality disorders.
I mean, it's hard enough keeping up with people that's only got one personality.
Now I gotta keep one person that's got multiple and two different individuals around here, right?
Like these bitches need mental health.
Yeah, well, I think like three personalities like the norm is like we have the persona we have I do not want to be here
This is okay. This is a sexual woman abuse
Zostos, Zostos she gay
I drew a picture I drew a picture of a Mita
it's beautiful leader it looks like it looks like easy on camera the guy you
know that guy but easy no easy this is gonna be easy to look like easy to
Wait, I'm sorry that one easy the letter easy. Oh, yeah. No, this is a simple line, right?
This is in the line. Yeah. Mm-hmm. I like it though
I like you to print that out and put on the refrigerator, man. Okay. I got it. Look at it
It also looks like Jesus Christ. Okay. Look at there's at least as little Jesus Christ, too
Jesus Christ, oh
We are Lord Lord bless us all electronic Christ. I'm an electronic use
I'm gonna pray to that tonight
That work
In Korea we believe in Jesus Christ you do Jesus Christ II
Yeah, can you, yeah, Asian.
Okay, let's race this.
Okay, never mind.
Okay, um...
That's beautiful.
Thank you so much.
I mean, how is everything doing?
It is so nice.
It's beautiful.
Yes, thank you so much.
Oh, look at, we're all in the middle of this beautiful scenery too.
Show us what's amazing today.
Oh, everyone's watching.
Can you tell me the name of the dickhead?
Like, can they call it Aldo?
You're here
Yeah
How are you be elder? I miss you. Where have you been?
I
Was on a same-man panel last night then I jumped on beaters today, but I've been I've been good
I've been chilling. I'll be more around this week, you know
I'll be more around this week. I'm just trying to figure out why why be the actor like nah, you good. You're good
Like like a different person
Are you here because the breast signal psyche sent down? I don't know who that beat up bitches
I hope she dies and rocks and hell, but who's the guy in the left that called grumpland to pump along?
I don't know. I think that's fine. You just disassociated with her body and
Happens sometimes what happened? Yeah, okay. You're a lot common. He likes karaoke. Yeah, he likes for Asia
Yes, he loves
Asia
It's I don't even know if you're Croatian let alone
It's pronounced Croatia. Okay. Anyway, I need to see girl
Okay, what are we doing guys? Okay, look?
Look over there, Mita.
Run, run, run, guys, run.
Sure.
All right, you should do a little R-R-R-O at the boardwalk.
I will, maybe.
Yeah, you go to the boardwalk at the thoughtboxer.
It's not open right now.
It's all closed.
And I sleep on the phone, and we all just relax together.
Yes.
Well, go go to the go to the party of
Here in another eight hours the pier will open for the happy hour
Unlike I look forward to that is like every day every day I watch dude you do that
Oh, that's so amazing. Oh my God, my favorite. Thank you, oh my God.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I made that. I made this one. Well, this is on the back so you can't receive it.
Very nice. Okay, so what are we doing?
Let's see
chat seems to be on a tangent right now about
Staying up a lot for a long time from what I understand. That's the bad part about meth
Specifically is not like the meth directly. It's that you stay up for days and weeks on end or whatever and then just never brush your teeth
And that's why habitual meth users have you know teeth problems. This is because they
Stay awake for so long and just forget to brush their teeth essentially. No, no, you should
floss lots of lots of floss and
Brush your teeth
You can always get the nearest
No
Floss factor you eat and brush your teeth
like three times today
Zostos CJ
You to parles France right?
It sounds like some satanic language.
It's just we, they shouldn't feel it.
I mean, your friend is French.
My friend is French.
I want to talk to you.
I don't, I don't talk like that anymore. I, because I, I'm Koreshia.
No, you're not Koreshia.
Alright.
Psyche, the, the, I think the biggest thing against my, like, straight card is that my favorite,
Shut the fuck up, nobody cares.
One of my favorite movies is technically musical.
the night before christmas
is technically musical
hey grandpa, can i talk for a second?
i'm sorry, seki
good morning
seki, they got me blocked in your chat
they got me hidden and blocked in your chat
who are you?
I'll look, I'll look, I'll look
into it. Who are you? Who are
you? So, you got a mod that's
going around. Who are you? You
don't come. Who are you? Who
are you? Because I was just
in your chat. Who are you?
What's your name?
Life. Life is not gonna
He seemed very unrated. He does
He should get a
You easy easy easy easy take a breath
I wanted to say hi
Let the blood pressure lower though chill, bro. It's just the internet don't don't freak the fuck out over a block
No, I'm absolutely fine. You guys getting the wrong idea. I was just trying to
I was just trying to get a couple fill skin was talking. Yeah, I didn't want to come off like a dick
Obviously, you know they got mad from yesterday
I don't want to be here any more longer. I don't want it. I don't want it anymore. It's too much for in Croatia. We we have peace and
And
Oh, no, I usually sign into one of my 420 sock accounts
If that shit happens I don't worry about it. Yeah, I don't like to do that
I keep my counts everybody knows me and what I say I stand on well all four hundred and twenty of my soccer
Counts have exiled in them. So, you know it's still
Oh
They have something like these like a lot. What do you mean by suck accounts?
They often hit accounts accounts. Yeah, we use the top shit the people
Yeah, oh
Was going back to like win sock
Just a thing in the 90s. Oh, yeah, no, no
We got figure out a way to bring that terminology back to
Yeah, I know I'm the like calm guy
Or somebody else reference something that was from, you know, I
Was
That they they blocked me from because I was arguing with somebody I
Don't know
What's your blood pressure like?
What mine? I'm in Croatia. I'm in Croatia. It's fine. I'm just outside smoking a cigarette. That's pretty good, man
And you should stop stressing out in the morning
No, man, I did my workout. I did my workout. I mean don't let's right now. Was it push day or pull day?
Push
You'll skip legs
Justin by Justin tries
I can buy tomorrow
How many guys are in here from like a America
Oh, no, Texas
Texas here or one to the guy that the one to the left there the
Hostess was from America
Texas you can you can see the flag. It's Texas that the guy that the one the host is from America
Well, I'm not sure you'd have to ask him
He looks
What is the where's the horse with the where's the gay guy like to talk to the gay guy
He's fallin ball. That's it. I think people block me because they got mad because I said it's like he was my gay guy
And this was my channel because I came up here
Well, you're definitely not his gay guy. What the fuck is this beat-tah you keep saying beat-tah beat-tah. I don't know fucking this bitch beat-tah
Where's that fucking gay guy? I like him. There's a gay guy that does a terracotta
Yeah, I see them. Okay. I'm sorry. It's like, you know, it's trying one more piece now. Keep it held down
Yeah
I didn't answer your name there. I have to look back. I'll look back in a little bit. I have to like check again
I'm sorry. I didn't see but I did I did add two new emojis to the chat. I put like a the evil eye
icon and I put the
SOS icon, so if you need help in the chat
Can you see me in chat SOS?
I need SOS. My throat hurts so bad.
My throat hurts.
Why does your throat hurt?
Yeah, I don't know
No, beat is or wait, what do you what do you want? I don't know. I need
Your name on here is beat as kitty's bkg, what would you like to be that's not that?
They do that. They tricked me like they say, I'm like that, which
Wait what?
That's what that's what that translated to she's number one throat go
Yeah, if you're gonna do it you gotta be number one on it, right?
Yeah
Cock-a-doodle-doo does these
Louvets
We're the cute kick-eye
one second be this kitty. I just I
Crafted something to say
To you so you could understand
Everybody's calling you beta. I'm asking you what do you want to be called instead of beta because that's your name on the panel
It's beat as kiddies BKG. That's what the horse changed it. And my name is not beta. It's meter
it's going to be a team a team we say back a team personality disorders bro this is
just something you got to deal with mm-hmm yeah you have a you know mpd a
distorted oh boy I go I don't know I don't know her voice gets deep and she
Yeah
Okay, I thought we I thought he said I'm
Hey psyche are you there? Yeah, I think the safe thing to do is just to mod that account so I don't get blocked and
Okay. I'll consider that very carefully. No, he wants a super wrench. That way, he can abuse the older
Okay, are you correlation in correlation? Okay? No, I put another photo and another energy and put it in some teeth, okay?
What do you think guys check it out? Oh, I need I need to get a beat I can beat her
That's her phone bone voice you should try to like interact with it sexually I guess
No, we don't I don't like this. It's a AI. I
Don't know. It might be a
Hmm interesting. I know you know how we like to see what we can do with AI
We'll break a jailbreak and then apparently
You can hear about what happened with the grok, you know that the um, yeah, yeah, yeah, I do I do
I'm I want it. I want to get the entire story. Yeah, we don't want to know everything
It was giving back some answers, you know grok
And uh, pretty racist, you know, oh rock is rock 3.0 is a real race. I know I know I guess he put out
4.0 though. He tried to get down real quick, and I think 4.0 is already up
What group of people is rock racist?
Yeah, this is like real life events all of them that don't happen around this drunken circle
Is it like the whole human race he's racist against?
Whites, you know, and um, yeah, if you if somebody has a
Computer can Google it and uh, it'll it'll kick some good conversation
My country would say I see the top of the teeth, but she didn't know country
Just bow down to a little tiny country. I am from Croatia
The I want to give a grokka virus and it tell me he's a little bitch cuz it's just a common code
Just say are you from Croatia? Yeah, oh, okay
not funny
Not funny. No, honey, honey
I come from this country doesn't mean have to make you a matter of it
You're too much
Well, you said a thing like seven times. I was just confirming that it's still same thing not you
Oh
Okay, I go back to my country. Is that what you want? Thank you. We can tell us whatever you are with the cats
Whoa rocks not here
Marry me. I go
I go back to Russia
Is grok in the room right now? Can you can you point at it? Let's move back to you go back to your boarding, California?
American life as whole
Okay, let's do it
I'm it. I'm it. You want to you want to challenge me? Yes, I'm in Texas here.
It's me than whore. Okay. Bye. Go first. I challenge you to take me whore.
First we get teach me who are the money. That's an interesting
You cannot teach me you love my Croatian accent somebody paid a kickoff Mita, please
I'll get you back guys whoever kicks off Mita
Someone put that accent to
Yeah, she's not Croatian. I don't know where she came
I said, Jezeleetierrevaat.
That's French, right?
No, that's RU Croatian in Croatian.
Oh, OK.
No, I don't speak Croatian.
I look it up.
I think I'm pronouncing it correctly.
He cannot pronounce anything correctly.
That's not how you say it.
He said it like this.
You complimented me on my pronunciation.
He said it wrong.
It's very nice.
Thank you.
He complimented me on my pronunciation the first few times.
So, like, until you knew I was looking it up,
you thought I was doing it very well.
Or you wanted me to think that you thought that...
I give the best manipulation.
Right there.
Mida, he caught you.
So which one was it?
Were you...
for no reason like trying to manipulate or what's going on?
You need a hug?
Yes.
I mean that's fair.
In creation we need a hug.
Why don't you hug the Bosnians I
Don't have any right now being them from going to the beach
Bosnia goes all or Croatia goes all the way around Bosnia. They can't like they can't go to the beach
That's like
This Croatia said nah, you can't go to the beach. We have all the shore
Well, you know how that conquering happened no motherfuckers conquered all the land around them and then military was like
You know what? I think we're just gonna stop here
I bet it'd be funny though
You know historical context of course not every book that people was in fear like they're gonna destroy the last of us
Our whole race is gonna be gone next thing
You know, they just start building their cities and shit and letting them have all that shit in the middle
Keeping a prisoner for eternity
Shit that's fucked up. Is that the only country that's like that
It's got one
That's gotta be that was like a asshole move that was intentional that couldn't have been by
Yeah, yeah, I am
I'm a happy asshole
Why do you smoke crack right now?
I heard a lighter. You smoking crack?
Is it crack?
Crack? Crack cocaine?
Crack in America?
Crack anymore?
You, you did crack. We heard it with the lighter.
You did crack cocaine in America.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Let's go see Vacheros Popil.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just thought I think I showed us.
In America, we like to roll our crack in like handpaper.
And add a little bit of cinnamon and butter.
I do smoke your crack out there and call it.
Mita, how do you smoke your crack in Croatia?
Oh, shit, it's bestial day, like today, all the day off from work.
Yeah, I took day off today.
For bestial day?
It was very hard.
It remind me of the day I take for my ancestors when they did the bestial days.
Well, that's crazy because that's a national holiday. You're supposed to work. Yes, I did. They took it all in every country.
Why are you talking crack again? I hear keep hearing crack and lighter like crack head.
I'm going to crack. I'm going to
crack. I'm going to crack. I'm going to crack.
She got visa and passport
Why am I still here can my mom help me come to the United States too? I don't I don't know
He wants to know about me test problems with somebody
What was that case
No, never mind
I don't see that, I don't see that, I don't know, who left that one?
Pillar you're you're a little bit muffly you're just your mic is a little bit muffled
Yeah, we couldn't hear you brother
Oh, sorry my bad, uh, yeah, never mind. Oh, that's way better. Yeah, it's not important never mind. I'm sorry about that
Yep. Typical KZ fashion. Gotcha.
KZ is doing cocaine again?
No, I think he's mouth fucking that freshness in that photo next to him.
Hmm.
By mouth fucking you mean eating it or no mouth fucking it. He's it's okay though. He's gonna throw it back with
mouth functioning
Yeah, that's what we call it for co word around here
But what what part would you I mean on a fish they don't they don't have dicks or anything what?
I mean, he is mouth fucking it.
Yeah, I think that's true.
Oh, other way around.
Okay.
My bad.
But no, that one is actually a big fish.
It was going back.
The one before that, though, was a bad catch.
It was a little fish and it went into its eye.
It was hard to get out.
It was brutal.
It was fine.
I tore it back, but I think it lost an eye.
So he's playing a game of blind fish out there, huh?
What kind of fish did you? Oh, I just I just woke up and I saw why that the guy the host is like frozen in the sky
Like licking in the air like like that. What's wrong with him? No
No, it's the it's the host bunker flunger you hold the host of the channel
Roppelstilts skin is
Yeah, yeah, you the host what I do
Yeah, the most are you you own the channel? Yeah, you're in the whole spot. Yeah, the new
Okay, okay
No, I don't have buttons. I'm not the host. I'm not
I'm doing that. Well, this is your channel
No, it's not my channel. I'm not live if you're
You're there on the top and it's okay. Thank you for doing it like allowing me there
I'm I will keep it down while
While tarot is gone. Mr. Psyche tarot is gone
What's a federal gone? I
Channel cats early today one was four pounds and one was seven they were a little bit different
Hey grump will pull up in a brain and pull up some digital tarot cards and read us some tarot cards
I that's not that's not my bag at all
Why up there it says on and tell her reader
It does say that
Why are you gay? It's a Monday morning?
I don't know. I just woke up one day and it happened
I see on the on the channel title. I see a Monday morning open panel sending love not
Yeah, but they did the channel says
Something suck cool
Taro our cones
I'm sorry. I'm hard of hearing. I didn't understand
I call our co-carot cards
Like that
Okay. Oh
Oh, you know what?
hang on okay maybe maybe this is the thing you're gonna do one for us okay
we're gonna get a reading from this look for like yeah okay so read my fortune
hang on let me figure out
Let me figure out how to do it real quick. Yeah, I'm gonna pull up some I'm gonna pull up a tarot card thing
Very good
I know I know I know I know grandpa the tarot card grandpa reader
Tarot grumpals. Yes, good
Where do we cash up
Oh, I still got to figure that out
You can give me like subs on kick or something that's the best way
Right now I need to pick up I'm the worst streamer ever. I'm
I haven't been live at all since Friday
I'm a delusional. I thought I am here on something on your panel
Tonight you're talking to me. You're talking to me. I talk to you. It's just your channel
Okay, hang on
Read me a card today. Yep, we're gonna do we're gonna do tarot
A grumble tarot.
I just need, I need just a moment to get everything to work and then make it
like there. Yeah, that and then
Oh, here we go
So tell me when you want to tap no no
tap okay tap
now now
Which so choose six cards?
Oh
Six six card
Which which cards you want that's one two so the first one
Six card
Okay, you have to choose six total so six card six card. I choose two
I
Yes, you need to choose six cards
I'm gonna I'm gonna stay numbers and I'm gonna read from left to right and I'm gonna do numbers
So I say the numbers that you want just say that or repeat the number. Okay?
1, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, OK, and then 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0, OK, there is no zero.
So I'll do 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0, 0, in my country, Google Earth.
So we got one more to do.
It's not an array, sweetie.
It's counting starting to
So five four three two one in that order is what you said first
seven six six is the last card you would like is that what you said seven six five four three two one nope you have to set six five four three two one that's what you did first so what are you doing now six six six six six yeah thank you so much so much for your like
Okay, so you got the world, the lovers, the moon, the hanged man, justice, the empress, these aren't, this isn't, like, five appendicles, this is, okay, whatever, here's, we're gonna do this reading, dramatically.
Five appendicle, I don't like that one.
How you feel yourself, about yourself, card one, the world.
You're about to reach or are already enjoying a period of total fulfillment, wholeness,
and satisfaction, the arrival of your heart's desires.
You feel satisfied with what you've already achieved and are enjoying the rewards for
past efforts, a time of happy outcomes, material wealth, and greater spiritual awareness.
That's how you very very sexy
Card two is what you want most right meow lovers
This card suggests the what you want most this at this time is to know what choice to make
Carry on as you are or take a risk
The risk offers excitement and change and staying as you are well, you know what that has to offer
Dare to love or dare to live I
Could go there
Part three your fears
Much I don't want to hear the theories
It's
This isn't
Lies and insecurity are likely to be prominent in your life
At this moment you are afraid of being deceived and feel that you're being misled
Possibly by a troll on some panel reading your tarot cards right now
Frustrated
These that may seem charming, but are only out for their own gains
Your turbulent emotions are muddying the waters step back and try to find clarity of mind although this may seem difficult
The moon does help it to illuminate the way and don't worry. It'll turn out. It'll turn out all right in the end
It's good yeah
I like it hard for even, uh, you know, I know like I get told like today like, you know
You told that you told that and they don't care. It's okay. It's good. Good. Good cards for you and me
You told me is
What you have going for you hard for to
Why are you talking like that? You know, okay, who's beta?
Who are you? She said she must be me. This must be me
My I don't I don't know me either. I'm from Croatia
Excuse me
Very good. Wait Croatian lady. We're doing a terror reading right now. We're halfway through
Okay
Okay, if you can bear with me
What do you have going for you Mita?
I'm not Mita, I'm from Croatia.
Oh, okay, so I'm in Croatia and I do everything.
Don, wait, are you from Croatia?
Yeah, I go to work and I like to go to Croatia.
Oh, I never would have guessed.
Mita, what you have going for you is the hanged man.
Think of that sounds good, okay? It sounds wonderful. Well hang on, let me let me read it.
With patience, this passive time, this time of feeling in limbo and indecision will pass on
then you'll know what decisions to make, what or whom to let go and how to move on.
That sentence ended in preposition or a dangling participle.
That is not for potential in my life whatever self-sacrifice you have to make you will feel better and stronger person for it
So sacrifice that thing. That's what this card is saying
Whatever self-sacrifice you have to make you will feel a better and stronger person for it
We got two left five what's going against you oh justice
Things just aren't going your way. Are they Meeta?
Even if you are in the right or the victim of foul play, you won't win this one.
Oh.
Take care of whose advice you take and beware of being motivated solely by self-interest.
No, my one is coming now.
Anality, Nita, we've reached the climax of this card reading.
Oh my God, I'm going to have an orgasm now.
I'm scaredy.
You don't like the outcome.
The empress.
Yes.
This is truly creative and fertile time.
I am the empress from Croatia.
Expect the best if you're considering having a child, creating a new job, business...
No, no, no, no, I don't have anything to do with it.
The Emperor symbolizes abundance, joy, and happiness, and reassurance, a firm foundation for future progress.
And thus is the conclusion.
We've reached the completion event of this tower reading, Mita.
This was for Mita?
Yes, this was for you specifically. You chose the card. My name is not me to ask or
You said you wanted to be me to you didn't like beta and you said somebody changed your name and it's supposed to be beta
You said beta. I didn't say that
There's no such name in Croatian it called me to
So every card that you read was a waste of your time and you told yourself
Nope, you chose him so it's yours
You trolled yourself
It doesn't matter what your name is
You chose him
No, no, the logic is flawless
You chose the card so it's yours
Regardless of whatever your name is
This is perfect logic
You cannot argue this
Because it's indefensible
You chose the cards
I'm from Croatia
Wait are you from Croatia?
Yes, oh
Okay
You chose the cards there were your cards and I did a dramatic reading of them you're welcome psyche
Well, I will say compared to the reading I got from psyche like I think three to four days ago
This was very good. Very elaborate more attention. I like it and I like it
One two three and he just goes hello. Hi, how are you and that's his reading
No, nobody said that
and the guy psyche goes, uh, I, hello, one, how are you, two, you doing good, three, yeah, great, and that's what's reading.
Okay.
Where do I donate to you?
Uh, you can't right now or you can where do I subscribe? Where do I find this to the quad reader again?
Uh, can we do family can we do like
Who is that?
I mean if you want to go and watch anything when i'm live on youtube that would help out
I help I help a lot money someone kick is the best way right now
I don't I
I'm like halfway through setting up cash app and stuff, but don't yeah, don't worry about that
Bobby I
Like the one day I came to the channel and you had this girl named beta. She was like
Very stupid stupid
She will see time after time
What is the retarded guy psyche channel awakened?
We're on that channel now beta the the gay retarded guy. Yeah, we're on now. I wouldn't pour them on him. He does not come up right now
Where is psyche psyche you there
I'm gonna
Meet up. I'm Mita. I'm gonna perform on you. I want to tell you
If you don't know mr. Seiki taro
Why you have the beat a beta like that like a evil meter
I wanna porn bomb Psyche today.
That's a bad idea.
The tarot card didn't say you got it.
You, the guy, what do you call it?
Carrow, tarot, whatever, you did good.
But the guy, Psyche, he does not pay attention
to the panel.
I'm gonna porn bomb him.
Come on.
The first rule about doing that kind of thing is not announcing it beforehand, but also the cards didn't say you should do that, so maybe listen to the cards, you know.
Let's get it.
Okay, ready?
Oh, yeah.
On a three-beater, we'll all show our nuts.
I just show my, I just show my tits from Croatia.
What does that mean?
You have your camera on now.
Why would you start?
I did.
I delivered.
Mr., Mr. Psyche.
I have to thank you because I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm loving this right now.
Psyche.
The very first karaoke stream I did was like when you like you were having some technical issue you started it
That's where I got the idea. Like and I just
And you had like your your stream died or something or you you disconnected or something and I said well, okay
I want to keep doing this. So I was doing a bunch of impromptu ones
And then this past what Thursday last Thursday did my first announced one and it's great. Everybody loves it
The karaoke string yeah, I gotta hop by when you do it. What day do you do it?
Well, I did one last Thursday
I think I'm gonna do it like once a month on like the regular and instead of didn't DJ an hour is do it like I
started at
200 or 8 a.m. Texas Standard Time, which is central for you know, you
Yeah, I gotta do it to pop song. I mean, that's fine
Do whatever
Yeah, do whatever you want
Yeah, I'm just I was just thanking mr. Mr. Sike. Oh, yeah, well, you're welcome. You're a very welcome
I kind of I kind of added to the idea. Wait, Mr. Sike, you come back
Yeah, it's a thank you back. It's a thank you kid back. I was
You all day long
I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back
Just reading words psyche while your head is currently on the side like that
Is it curly? You have one curl hanging there to the side like
Yeah, I'm Superman
I don't know any more
In the Superman or I'll tell for one of the two of them. I forgot
Can't believe I'll tell us the opposite way it goes up
Okay, well, however it goes I look like terrible. Okay, anyway, that's not you are very
But your hair looks like very like a mushroom like today
Bad she said you're a pretty fun guy, right you're from a mushroom everything. I'm a mushroom. Okay, you're pretty fun guy
Yeah
Yes
You're
Look at the positive sides of the spectrum
Well
Leave your hand off my fun guy. Okay. Hey guys. Oh my gosh. Well, I can't let you touch your phone guy
Good. I don't want you to keep your hand out. Nobody's going to
Unless you're sitting in a hot tub two feet apart then
I say out of the house, I was like, he is very, very, very upset and jealous of Mita and our relationship.
Our relationship is not going to last anymore, psyche.
Oh, well because you're gay and I'm gay
We'll make it we'll make it work. We'll make it work. Here we go. Do a negative equal positive
Yes, the penis and I know until we try we don't know until we try
Ah, no, thank you very much.
I didn't get in many buttholes.
I don't want to try that.
No, no, not your butthole.
Ew.
I don't want it.
Your dick has been too big.
No, I don't want it.
No more.
I would have to.
I don't want it to.
I don't want your dirty dick to be in me.
Brown.
I want to show brown.
I don't want it.
I want to take your magic stick and like do like have a card with us. Okay, you too. I
Don't do telecards. I don't have a magic stick
What are you two?
You just did tarot cards meet
No, they were bad guy grandpa Pooley
Now you chose him that's it that was yours I picked it
Yeah, I'm laying in bed. I'm sleeping under the sheets. I don't I don't have any cars in my house
Yes, I am you chose them you're sleeping right now
It's correct. I'm not God that is very correct under the covers
Psyche
You were supposed to come cuddle with me there, okay, let's go
Wait who's gonna be the big spoon
He doesn't like I don't want to fuck him in the butt. I just gonna cut oh, okay. Yeah
Like I'm like a huge pot or huge part of the I don't want to be that smaller spoon is I did definitely not
Thank you very much. Yeah, it is like a measuring cup. She's like a measuring I give out. She's like
well, too too, uh
You can't measure in cup rumble. How long were you asleep on your stream a couple weeks back? I saw you pass out
Oh, it happened to you. Now you're like me. You're falling asleep, too
No, excuse me, sir. I was one of the originators before leave streams on twitch. We're even a category. Yeah, I was falling asleep
Sometimes
Yeah
The funny thing is when it's when you're not intending to do a sleep stream
Which is which is a whole ass category, but when you're not intending to do it
Yeah, you get decent viewers and like sometimes
Good fundraising on it even because people trying to wake you up
You you have a Amazon wishlist grandpa grumpy dude. Yeah
Everyone can get your neck pillow. We get your neck pillow for your Amazon thing.
Everyone keeps telling me to go back to sleep.
Yeah, we get your neck pillow. You turn kind.
Oh, I'd have to wear that while I was still alive and that, but I just...
Anyway, you are still very good for the terrorist, but my favorite terror is the short, fast and quick like the Cycord.
And he's going to come and spawn me.
Fast art and girthy is how you like your tower readings?
I like it very, very quick, long, and then after we just spawn together, like that's it, you know?
Do you like to choose from the front or the back of the deck?
Uh, whatever that psyche prefers. I think he prefers from back of the dead
Ladies choice ladies choice. Okay, then the front the front. Okay. Thank you
From the front this time it was like just straight off the like, you know
Up cut off the front six cards
Yeah, we weren't in that order. Yes, look card look cards go up five four three two one six was her
Four three two one three six. Thank you
That sounds to Tana. I'm gonna go back to my country. It's like a different lit like I don't know what time it is here
I don't know what country is that?
It's a cause extent
A whole lot to your brother. You're from Croatia. Oh
Very very racist of you. I am not but a fucking wife. I'm not fucking from there. Very nice. Very nice. Sorry
Those are good. I'm sorry
Kazakhstan's one of the biggest
Croatia and you blew my fucking whistle and you said I'm from fucking India. Everybody knows the word
I know I said you look like it. You look like an Indian
Right, that's what I said. You thought you're from India
You look like a you look like a one of those tomahawk Indians a page a white Indian
Whatever I don't have much dollar I can count like four dollars and twenty five cents with quarters and thumbs
Are you talking about your shaved or unshaved? What are you talking about?
I'm talking about your hair cut.
Oh, okay.
Oh, 25 cents? Okay.
Yeah, this is not making any sense at all. These numbers are sort of arbitrary
When I was a screener trying to break into Hollywood some come somebody if they're maker
We'll say something about money. I would say I don't even care about the money. I just want to work
That's what you should just shape you. You should just shave your head if you want to be I should I should I should
I should shave with a love. Wait, what are you doing? You're gonna you're gonna cast me and I'm gonna shave my face
Yeah, yeah. Oh, okay. Well
Yeah, we'll do it at the same time
You guys want to do that on screen? We'll do we'll do five dollars per stroke. And uh, you know
You know
Oh that you get pricey be able to save each other, right?
Yeah, but it's just it's like a little you know we get to do it for ourselves though
$5 per stroke. I am not beta. I know you had a lot of I hate lots of hate for beta
But I am like a operation friend of your and you were storming to me and
Diverting your anger from beta to me your friend on the panel was nothing but nice
He did he was nutting 7 5 4 8 2 1 6 7 reading for me all good. No
And, I don't know, it just turns out to be a good day.
I said nothing, you go to that vagina.
Okay.
At all.
All of your chakra.
Me too.
Everybody wants to meet it.
We all know that it happened to your vagina.
So nobody wants to look at it right now.
Wait, hang on.
What happened to it?
Like, was there a steam accident or what?
Lisa what happened what happened music explains. They're like third-degree burns or I don't know
You should ask your psyche what happened to my vagina. I don't I don't actually
She said she said she like she was using like a like a piece of dynamite as a good dildo and then her
Her vagina landed up in South Carolina or something. I don't know. It's a limerick
That's oh
Yeah, I like that was some sort of
not poetry, but something about like trying to happen it happened to me to our beta I
Don't know I have to ask me that you told me the story once it was very sad
uh because uh beta beta called and said that happened to your butthole and your
asshole was like uh excluded because you got around so many times and uh a big you know big big
Wait, what if you were expecting it to be like a quarter stick of dynamite and get your you know, you're you're you're
Your tits in Brazil and your vagina in North Carolina, but it's just be a road. Oh, yeah, but what if it just turned out to be a road flare?
Oh, yeah, well that didn't then it would be like now
Then it just
Well now it's because you were waiting a lot of time because it would never happen
But hold on one second. Yeah, you just just be waiting the whole time
Yeah, hold on once again, I just get it down right well just because you're waiting and you're wasting your time waiting
Hold on once again. I got
Limerick I got to get the same right now
All the way you got a limerick it queued up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I have to want to find out it's
It's a very small country in Croatia and very small to come to and where do you go?
Like America is big and huge and loose, so we will come to your America.
You know how small it is it's very girthy America is huge big a big place
Lot of people in there like, you know
all diversities. In Croatia, we are very clean, little small, like not too many.
No, no, no. Croatia is very girthy for how, what the size of it is in the population.
Not too America. You know, look at the expoundation of the channel. It's huge.
Borat's from Kazakhstan or the character that is Borat
My wife
You slap it a base
Or I should win
You look like this
My babe
I don't know. They look like beta basically. Okay. So anyway guys
You've been doing this for two and a half hours we get it here. Yeah, you know
It's been two and a half hours
It wasn't funny
You know you're no Belki Bartokamas
You're very jealous of beta
You sound like, um, you know, you sound like a British, you know, queen. I mean, I didn't know it
I'm sorry psych. I respect the commitment to the game
I like to guide better the commitment to the game guys and
the give I give up to the gay guys
I don't know
You gotta know when stop not funny. It's okay. It's okay. You're for you. It is funny. It is funny. It's funny
Okay, I'm going to talk like this so that I don't know like I'm not the Tina from Puerto Vico. Okay. How about that?
That'd be funny. No.
What do you do? You're a team for the competition of the Accent of the Correcio?
You're not funny.
I'm Canadian, eh?
Hey, I'm hanging out with you, eh?
Yes, that's right.
If you put her backstage and change the name,
That'll fix it because then the bit is over
I mean at least that's how I would operate and I'm assuming Mike
Beats has what I already said beat his kiddies, but what's the hell?
You want you to write character? You're not you're a meter. You were beat it all time. You silly goose
Hello
Are you who are you talking to the guy to the last of you? Yeah, he looks like a silly goose cat
Me too. I am a silly goose cat. How did you know?
You're you're all come on
It's like, he's a psychic now.
Everyone is psychic.
Hey, Loki, how are you?
Everyone has to be a dude.
Oh, hi, baby, it's okay, man.
Hold on a second.
So what are we doing guys? Are we gonna do some fun?
Strip poke or something. What are you doing? Oh, I got you, babe
Bars against humanity that include the most foul things that you could ever
Cheerless Kate. Are you getting sick of me or is he getting sick of you?
I think when Mita and Mita combine together you will never be shit
You will never be equilated to, uh, you know
Any things that I don't know no in our country
And the ugly hog fat whore. Are you talking to are you talking to why are you talking to them?
Kate the whore
I
Don't know. It's what was happy. She's like been doing a bit for like
She cuts me out
Hello summer good morning
Good morning. How are you all? Oh living a dream, you know
Yeah, I haven't some doughnuts this morning after coffee
Oh, I saw you eat some doughnuts. Yeah, that looks very sugary and
Like carb ready to get your energy on for you know a long full day of
streaming
Well, I'll just in for a couple more hours
Hmm
hours today
And I have trouble consuming enough protein in a day for what I'm supposed to even when it's like the only thing I consume
Just so much protein to eat
Try liquid. Yeah, I know I can't I can't eat
Shakes and like protein fortified milk in those shakes like
I'm supposed to drink 300 grams of protein a day. I can barely eat like 20, you know, so it's crazy
300 no
Twice twice twice twice your weight or twice your number of your weight and so you if you're under weight
So you can gain weight, right? Are you in metric or what like I'm a hundred and eighty two grams is my my goal
Right, dude. I'm not I'm six three in like two thirty. Well, I don't go by grams
240 right now, which I got my stones or pounds your stones
so we have a stone is about 20 pounds per or 20 kilograms per stone, but I'm like I'm actively lifting also
, as you can see a flex
and see here we go, but it's
my point
the lift, I think that you're lifting weights, there it is, yeah there it is and now that's
Well, I'm I'm shuffling things around right now
Is clear that there's a bag of boxes next to it that I'm shuffling. Okay. No, no, it's fine. It's fine. It looks it looks clean
It looks cleaner than my my uh, no, no, it's not clean at all. This is a room is a mess
Okay
Was that a kickoff beat it? No, I didn't kick off the show. Did I oops sorry beat it?
Yeah, but that voice was I had enough but come back
Let's see. Yeah, she was
She got mad. Okay, so who's this person's day? Oh Dave R. Hmm. I don't know who this is
It's fish taco something don't say the animal. Please
Why'd you dox my
I don't know. I mean, oh shit
Wait, I'm sorry. It was an accident. It was an accident. I didn't mean to dox it. Hello. Hello, Bita
Cuban girls and Cuban girls. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Just don't have your real name on there
I won't say it. I could confuse them. What are you thinking girls? I
Like I think Dominica Spanish girls Spanish girls
Black black. What's that song?
Living la vida look
Yeah, let me in dude. Just don't talk to my fucking
My first my thing is my email
Change your change your display name, and then that won't happen. Yeah
Your full name your full name your full name Dave or Dave or you already said it. It's out. Yeah. Yeah, but it's not a real name
You're right. You got
Stop talking. Don't talk to me
Okay, okay, don't just change your display name, and then it won't be a thing dude. My display name is fine
Okay
There's a beat right there. Don't show your dick to anybody and then no, of course not
Wait, this guy lives in a fucking filing cabinet, what is this you got your bow
That's Emma's I'm the people
You're like you're one of Emma's people. She lives in a filing cabinet. He lives in a filing cabinet
Well, yeah, yes, you like what she puts the souls in one so she takes home. Okay, I don't I think that's just a story
So, uh, hold on. Let's take it down a sign there. I own a lot of filing cabinets
Okay
Here we go. Here we go. What happened? Yeah, take it down racism systemic racism
Why are you being it doesn't so I'm born with it. I'm born with that
The world is more mixed in an effort, but I get bored this one. I'm trying to get it out
There you go, turn it off get there
Why won't you get that weeds getting way stronger nowadays? That's crazy. I know terrible terrible. There you go
It's because the racism
probably
They do like their weed
I don't see anybody. I don't see anybody. Where is everybody here? Oh, here. Oh, here.
Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh,
here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here.
here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh, here. Oh,
Oh, how are we doing and we got a friend back to
Guy, what's his name?
Sorry flex flex question mark. What are you are you are you rando rondo?
Yeah, okay. It's like I don't respect my brand. So I just changed my fucking name every I didn't care no more
I really don't okay, okay
Well, I try to pause about here, but it's like I'm tired
You know, I know it's hard out there. It's raining out here. It's dark gray. Like I'm trying
Oh, that's standard Philly behavior. So you're okay. It's burger
This first even worse his burger. Oh my gosh. Yeah, it's terrible
It's not my
Yeah, I'm like seasonal effective depression, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got summer right now. You just
Wait man man made climate change like that's what I'm thinking man. We don't need this
See how much fucking rain we got here. It's impossible that this is normal
Like
Making a change the cows. I mean, it's not the the government dude
I think what they're doing is raining us out. So the fucking middle
Like
So the history that we have even since the last ice age is dropping the bucket as far as the history of the planet, right?
Yeah, unless you think it's six years old which I mean, you know
Yeah, well
6,000 years old that's well that's according to like the mud you know the Quran and stuff like that so they have to say that
Let's
According to something and yeah, it's like the science that you just all of this will all just go by the religious
Aspects of it and we've got rock structures and prove it if you
if you think the planet is billions of years old and our recorded history of temperature that we know about is only maybe
a few thousand or so, then
OK, it would be a bit of a war with the industrial revolution, then hey, maybe
man doesn't have all that big influence,
these things were already changing and changing anyway without us.
Yeah, it's not anthropogenic.
That was a big word for me today
Like an animal
Progenic, let me see answer was animal or man home. No, it's man. It's man. Okay, man. Yeah, man. Okay, man
I'm made for dinner. Okay. Don't listen to me. I'm just a silly monkey. It's uh,
silly
Okay, right. I'm just a word. Are you looking enough from everybody?
Always learn
So, Paymore, okay, yeah, Kate will be probably, you know,
it'll probably be timed out sooner or later.
I have to go back into my stuff.
I can't do it right now.
I'm a little blurry.
How are we doing, guys?
I'm trying to figure out this.
Okay.
I'm going to log into my GogG account.
I can play some video games. I think beat is just mad because I called out Croatia for making Bosnians not able to go to the beach
Well, that's you guys. I'm not sure about the politics. So this is the other policy
I'm not sure. No, no, it's just if you look at the shape of the country. It just goes around Bosnia
Okay, and blocks them from going to the it's just it's a me. It's like a geography meme. That's all
Like it's a little bit like Israel
Okay, he must be a proud. Yeah, very proud
Really would be three three it's gone. What's going on?
I don't know no sakey. I want some stage. Okay. Oh, I take some I like some stage up
Where's my lighter
Oh, yeah, don't delete the Dono's mods
but
Yeah, well sure if it actually deletes it like the money coming in
But they paid for the message unless it's toss
Sometimes that happens, you know
Charge it to the game
Yeah, just I'm I'm not really
It's because it's bad form to really watch
other people's chat from
the panel instead of paying attention to the panel, but just happened to see a lot of
Thank you enter a bit a bit of banter happening about
Yeah, dude pay attention
Yeah, pay attention you're a chat psyche. What are you doing? I do I know I do I
You're making us work. I had on the screen. Please. Uh, you know, if you don't know
John I'm here be being stoned
What is that
It's just age
This is getting fucking weird. I gotta go see
Sage goodbye
Go do anything go do anything do any of the membership, please. I need to get a hundred. Please. Thank you so much
I'm just kidding. You don't have to do anything
It was misunderstanding. I never said you bite. Oh, thank you, Janet. Oh, hi dad. Thank you so much
Whoo apologies about the week. That's okay. You have fun
It happened fun with your man
Here guys go. Oh, he's calling
Either you're on the panel
So without any further tower readings around the panel just which G1 transformer do you think you identify as?
First generation
Nobody nothing
Well
Favorite pancakes
Just chime in.
I think adding chocolate chips or something like chocolate chocolate in general is okay during the baking process for like a protein, like a Kodiak pancake, or using that in like a waffle mix.
Waffles is a whole different topic.
Some people think you can just take pancake mix and put it in a waffle maker and then you got waffles, but it's a if you want to do it.
The right way, they do have a little bit of different recipes.
If you want to get deep into it, go to a waffle house, watch them, just get a cup of coffee
and watch them operate.
They'll probably even tell you the recipe for their pancakes and waffles.
Keeping trade secrets isn't really usually part of their forte and they're an American institution.
I
Tried to keep it down, but nobody wanted to talk about like I had three different topics
Nobody on the panel said shit chat eat chat got into it, but nobody said shit
Well, I was on the phone. I was on the phone taking care of something and it's not
You leave all I'll hold it down, but I mean I wasn't I was trying to leave
I was on the phone with somebody and
Okay
Hey, thank you so much
Yeah, okay a little bit stressful. I didn't mean to hurt you guys feelings
I didn't I don't even know when I put people backstage sometimes I just do it sometimes because it's like it's an impulse like oh
You know this person's like now. I want to talk. I just just like try and sometimes we're good from back
I'm sorry. Like I'm trying to defend people
Are you guys people put the people in the back for no reason and cause no reason so I mean it is what it is
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, she's she's very upset and everything it's like you know sometimes we need to take a little break from panels
I guess it would be like that
It's really tight up in a yes
What'd you say
Okay, I'm sorry
Okay. That's why it was too loud. Okay. There we go. Okay. Yeah. So I'm okay. Okay. Okay. So this is hold on
Let me show this to the right person. Let's see
Hello
Hi, hi, I just wanted to let you know I'm blocked under my
Kate show account
Be to block me after I sent that don't know and just so you know when you block a donator you do not get that don't know anymore
So not only is she
Fucking with your channel, but she's fucking with your revenue and I'm timed out on my other account
So you might want to do something about the mods who are modding with their feelings
Especially when it comes to donators
Okay, because she deleted me and Janet's
Donos
Okay
Okay. Well, I'll take it out. Um, thank you. I mean, it's like, I, I don't think I mean, I know, I know there's a reason there's like stuff going on. I can't like between you guys. And so it's like, I mean, it's like, I don't. And I know, you're gonna allow her to run your chat. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or or
from them. That sucks. Yeah, I didn't realize that. I appreciate knowing that. Thank you.
You're welcome. Have a good one. Thank you. You too, girl. Oh,
she didn't really want to hang out. Just let you know that that thing happened.
Okay, one second.
Okay, no, it's in poor form to
Interact with chat, but while you're not doing things. I'll just you know, take up time here
So for I mean, I am Bravo Sierra Bravo Bravo trademark. Why have moderators at all? It's pointless
well
the mods on any live stream
the
is
The way I see it is is you're trying to prevent that channel from getting clapped by keeping
things messages that are toss on the platform from
staying around and
That's the majority of it some people some streamers some content creators like to have their moderators have a more active role in like
Crafting a conversation and then in some spaces
They will just ban people who disagree with the content creator
I don't think that's that's not that's not here. That's just some space. There's so there's different levels of
I don't see her. I don't see her timed out. I don't see her hidden. So she's just I'm done. I guess I'm
Like, I'm up 10 seconds. It's fine
To take a dead air for you I got no I got you I was trying to I was looking back in the back chat
To see if it was banned and hey, are you back? Okay? Thank you, man
It's like, you know, they fixed it already. Okay. Yeah, so I look back. I didn't see it. So thank you guys
I've got good mods. I just really much rely on my mods to work on that stuff because I don't understand all the all the
You know ins and outs of the chat. Thank you guys. Thank you guys. I
Don't I wouldn't be mad. I want everyone to get along
I want this to be a place where everyone can get along. I don't want people doxing or fighting here. Let's just like work it out here
It was like
Neutral ground or something, right?
Comments are content. Yeah, they take it but sometimes you know people can like report
If there's a doxy in comments and stuff like that you need to keep making to make sure that the comments are appropriate and don't go against to us
And also don't get your the stream and the video that results from the stream to be demonetized
Right. Well, yeah, that happens a lot too. It'll happen if it gets no
Adults only or or you're just deleted or for private or even
Unlisted
I'm still a little bit new to YouTube and
things for a while, but
Yeah, things work and YouTube is a little different than other places. Yeah
I don't care if people think chat can affect your chat.
I don't know, maybe it can, maybe it can't,
but people can say like, you know, report things in chat.
I think maybe some people have had problems with that.
I'm not sure, I don't think it's a regular thing.
Maybe that's a thing.
Coming from a while back on Twitch,
you were 100% responsible for the chat
and that seems like kind of bullshit too.
But then they made it so that
Well, no, that was hang on that. You're not responsible for bot like getting bot followed
Because that would be a weaponized against channels or a little bit, but yeah content creators on twitch
I think are still 100 responsible for
Yeah, I know i'm still on you
Kick not as much, um, but yeah youtube i'm still
Exactly what to where the where the lines are for for chat. I'm not a hundred percent sure so
Don't listen to me. I'm just a silly monkey. Just for that month. I think I'm a simple monkey creator
Don't don't listen
No, I do you're a colleague or if you're a fellow colleague, let's see it says
Yeah, we'll say in your back chat all the monetization stuff exactly how much to make every every single part so you can check check
Like there's the your breakdown. Let's see
moderation permission, okay, perfect
Yeah, so everything looks good on my side guys. Do you have any?
Things to suggest I got emojis spaces for the box
I'm sorry. No, no, no, I got I got I got a boss. Are there bots in my cat?
How many people do I have in my chat right now?
No, I mean you're like your bots like it
I told you
Auto moderate like yeah, you got a moderator banning people
Yes, pretty much the only thing these days. Yeah, there's not very much you can do to get banned my show
I'm very very liberal. Okay
But if you know me, yeah, I think I can't kick you off the panel
Sometimes I'm not liberal at all and we can still hang out and have a good time, right?
No, I mean I'm not liberal. I mean just liberal as you know, I'm a liberal policy, but I
You're not really political
It's like you have freedom. I like freedom, but you know up to like the point where it's not gonna
No, it's like, you know within the terms of the platform and stuff
So you're you're free to do everything up until it steps on somebody else's freedom or within the confines of the platform on which
Yeah, exactly exactly exactly. So that's that's the
That's the differentiator if you blast. Why can you do this here not there? I think, you know
There are double standards or some channels that take other things more serious than others, but
We're all just trying to run our shows that we want here pretty much
Okay. Let's do that. Okay. Okay. Let's see. So, I have some donuts.
So, what do you think we all just speak Croatian for the rest of
Well, I mean, I don't, I don't know Croatian. So, that's a problem.
I don't know it. Give it to me, baby. Oy vey. Oy vey. You got it. That's it. That's Yiddish. That's Yiddish. Come on. Oh, no, that was the
the weird Al cover
the song that
I made it like I took his meme and I made another level deeper meme that's
That's the guy. Yeah, that was good. It was good. Yeah, right rabbit hole
This was it was an alley you hundred percent. Thank you other men
Okay, well
Let's see 63 people watching right now. Thank you guys for watching. If you'd like it subscribe by the way
Thank you. They love me like either people love me. I mean you you love you psyche
Well, I saw Kate just briefly say hey am I unhidden and then it vanished
Okay, if I need some I need if I need I don't I don't know it's like
No, I'm not the way that shit. I don't yeah, I'm sorry
It's terrifying
Yeah, the way I didn't mean it. I didn't mean this stuff. No, you're fine
You're like that's like stepping on a landmine of cow shit
Or like a guana shit. I'm not sure which is worse
Well, you believe that
Pardon my friend. So let's see kick started next new video promotion. Oh, this is cool. I
Get to promote the new videos now
Oh, yes, okay, you still are multi streaming right?
Yeah
Are you streaming on kick too, right? Yeah
Oh, yeah
Thank you weekend, but it's not it's not there right now, but I have I haven't I can start it right now
I can I can say yeah when you see my YouTube you should just style them on all
Like psyche underscore awaken or no, it's just like he awakens. It's like one. Oh, what's it might be under the
Yeah, I think it's just like you a week. That's why I see HG a couple years ago. I was like I was like he awakened
Oh, here we go. You get like a it's a different logo like like a box
Yeah, mm-hmm. Okay. Oh, yeah, okay you
I'm not sure if it's that's the right one, but I think that is where I want you said movie
up to my name. You're not you're not live but I can go like this I can go
I'm going to go simultaneously stream to this location. Yeah, I'm gonna have that right there.
Yeah, you see they get the new stream on like set up to like at least on the mobile it does.
There's kick.
Just um, and thunder thunder trousers. I did a deep dive on
highway to hell by AC DC a
week or so ago
and
It's totally season ticket, but the FCC has got let that slide for I
Don't know. I didn't say it. I don't I don't say I don't say I don't even curse
Okay, you're gonna mod just make sure it's yours. Yeah, they keep doing it to me too, psyche
Let's let's let's let's let's stop having you all out
The war is over people the war is over everybody go home. The war is over
Also, don't play highway to hell or any acdc on your channel. It'll be it'll block the video from
They'll cut it out, right
One of those whatever some parts of it just say that up on your stream, right?
And then they they copyright just that song out of you a lot. Yeah, don't they just clip it out if you don't do it
Yeah, you can't yes, yeah
No, no, no, no, it just blocks the video like it just it doesn't like nobody can see it
Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't appear. Yeah, until you fix it to where it can then be
Published and then after that maybe it's monetized
Psyche when I'm up here in that time when we were doing the karaoke like that that caught
So I
Yeah, but you could see that live and they just cut that part like I don't I don't I
Because the people have been people have been like, you know gotten stuff for my my life
But and I don't get it but the other people do so I don't know if that's anything to do
It's like what I'm monetizing like that protects me or something
But for some reason I don't have problems like what other people have I don't know
I don't think like the songs and stuff like that messes with your monetization
Yeah, I can't I can't I can't because you can get a community guideline strike
And then you can get we can get also people that do like strikes for like you're like
Oh, yeah
I just I just thought they would just take it down so you'd like you people you could it wouldn't be problem
Oh, no, they don't take it down
It's that they make it so that hey your your video can't be viewed anywhere. It doesn't happen while you're live
Okay, except sometimes it does and it'll say hey the stream has been temporarily suspended while if you're doing something
That's when you're doing it for a little while it'll say hey stream is temporarily suspended
But then after the stream is over the video will then not like nobody will be able to see it
You're everywhere or in certain places and it's all about the copyright and most of them are like
Hey, there's a copyright claim on this, but it doesn't impact you unless you're trying to monetize
You don't play the body videos you don't get hit as hard with that kind of stuff
Not exactly. It's like sometimes there's audio. Sometimes there's video. Sometimes there's melody involved
Like if you if you were to play on guitar highway to hell
I think you're still getting the same copy strike. Right. It's well
It just depends on like like I've never gotten like a strike on you by like a major company
Like by like a major by a major record company
It's always been by like a person putting it right trying to put it on and then it's okay now that now that's different than like
I'm like a community strike or something like that won't affect your channel. Yeah, it's just like uh
Right
Copy strikes at all these these are just literally like hey YouTube a Google just detected something
And we're just like you can't monetize it or we can't even publish it in anywhere now until you address this right
They won't they won't take it down the whole video down unless it's like a
Or it's like somebody made a personal complaint like you know, and then they
So what just happened to me so I mean it but I was able to get through it right so
you know so they do they are ferrets on some level because I was able to
give my side of the story and you know I'm fine now so
see you okay so yeah I hope that everyone's not just um hiding people in the chat I've
probably been having fun how's uh how's everyone doing the chat
I mean, I'm not like I was playing on crash and
I'm not like I was playing on crash and
Quite a while ago, but I'm I still haven't so I'm just gonna like
No, I haven't been going all night I started it probably have a time five or six this morning. Oh
Okay, you tube and twitch
Restream, yeah
This is biting content like I I could use OBS, but
This is just a lot easier because not then we could shadows all consolidated and everything's fun
Yes, and thank you guys. I'm so sorry for missing these super chats. I appreciate those super chats. Thank you so much for
For supporting the show
awesome guys, so it says
In a chat saying and see are they dancing?
Donating you're trying to buy influence. No, it became by influence. It's just you know
Just how your message read right is the proof coming in the pudding month hundred songs. They're all the same song
Thank you. Can you read our chat more? I know that I'm sorry the chat is really faster now
That's the one thing that I
I'll mod out to is anybody doxing anybody else because that's I
Believe that's toss on every platform too and along with just being bad in general
you don't you don't want that is anybody doxing anybody else in your chat or on your stream or anything right
We've had a bad. I'm pretty sure that's awesome every platform, too. So that's like just it's a good thing
I've been done
Doxing is the worst
So no
There's a doctor JC he likes you a lot you get a pat. I don't know not that I'd like to see a lot
It's just because I can't get
I don't know JC lowbrow this little power. I mean, I don't do it here. I don't know JC has no power here
That's why he's mad. It's like, you know, you're allowed to be in the chat though
JC
You just don't have a mod like I don't know and people don't need a mod stick the witties the witties
Oh, oh random guy. Thank you five for the filing cabinet guy. Thank you so much random guy
I mean
Well finally cabinet guy. That's like the uh, what is five for the filing cabinet guy like that five? I don't know
He said
Okay, yes, five. Okay, so I'm the filing cabinet guy like I mean, I'm in
You're the filing cabinet. Yeah. Okay. I'm there. I have a key to the filing cabinet
But they used to work for Emma. Well, you don't have any more mods. You control the one thing
They're calling him the file cabinet guy because when he showed his gym equipment, they were six people were saying something about the file cabinet
Yeah, I thought that too, but I don't want to assume anything about what other people do at all
Yeah, well
Good way to go. Okay, so
Do you see we have new new icons summer the new emojis?
I have the evil eye and I have like one that says
SOS was like if you need anyone in chat needs help you just type the SOS and I'll see your comment and I'll try to help
It's like you got a message in the back chat from about six minutes ago if you didn't see that one yet
Is that from Kate or no that one? Yeah. Yeah, I saw that. Thank you. I mean, yeah
Thank you so much. Thank you so much
Yeah, hopefully the mods are able to
Handle that is beat it. Are you timing out everybody come on?
person
Master trying to tell me okay home. You know are you being tyrant, you know, I just like I don't want to get sad because is this how you respect Croatia
Being a representative of Croatia, I'm looking for
Pretend you're not trying to keep those Bosnians from the beach now
Tell me it's not true
Oh, are you taking away the monster trying to help me hold I'm trying to get that. Hey, it's very slow my
Okay, I think you're fine. It's at a moderator turned on sub only mode, which isn't
Okay on YouTube, that's pretty normal
Okay guys, take a deep breath everyone okay
Know what did she dox though and chat today? I mean, I don't think she's dox in here
I mean, it's like I I understand but she's not doxing here. So
She's
I know it's like personal. I think why am I see to be to you. It's like you're triangulating me if you're asking me to like
Get involved in that. It's like, right. I
not triangulate
Grumpy of a channel up on a journal. Yes. I keep a paper one. No a channel. That's what we asked. Oh
Channel yes, I do
I'm
streaming off of this live right meow to
Twitch and YouTube I also do cake what's your YouTube channel usually Twitter and I'm gonna get back into rumble
I think I need to expand into tiktok too, and then there's like some other but it's a
Like I got it
Well, thank you. Thank you for linking
Oh
I'm already subbed to you. So okay, cool
Yeah, well the one one kt. Just link that's that's mine. Yeah, I know I forgot I'm a mod and I
We just did karaoke night, oh, that'd be fun. I like stuff like that then what Friday did a
I
Sorry, oh I see piranha was on Danny's getting strangers today. Oh
Sorry
How is everybody?
Okay, KZ. Thank you. I gotta get ready for work. I just left work. Okay, I love you. Thank you summer
I am locked inside a filing cabinet. It's kind of like Narnia or the
The Indian in the cupboard, if you remember that, it's kind of like that. I'm locked in here and you got to
Get a watch to help me get out watch me on my endeavors to escape from the filing cabinet
Can I um, you know, do you have a boyfriend or a girlfriend in the cabinet?
Or no, you're lonely in it
There's there's no other organic matter inside the cabinet
That is good to know. I was gonna be like, okay, maybe I'm gonna unsub if he has people in his cabinet
Yeah, it's not my cabinet. It's Emma's cabinet. I just have the key to it. I mean, it's like that's the whole thing
It's like I never give back
It is a fire it is a fireproof
It's it's in hell. It's the final cabinet in hell. So it is like fireproof, you know, it's very strong
The meme level is high though, you got to be able to handle high level memes for a month or so.
Oh yeah.
Okay, well we'll see.
Especially my Twitch.
Check out my Twitch trailer.
After I see your memes, I'll develop a Twitch.
I'll develop my own Twitch.
For your vehicles extended warranty.
Hey, there we go. It's not just me on the thing. It's like why am why is it me? But
Hey, I'll just roll with it. You don't think hey fine
Cat lover says energy vampires
Fred Alice or you're just this guy
He's sick. He sits here for hours an hour
I can sit here like you know, let me say anything for days and days a day as soon as I say Emma
He's right there. Are they so is it either like her like little like
personal flying monkey, or it's like some kind of really obsessed fan of one of us. I'm not sure.
Fred, you're trash.
Okay.
So loud?
Yeah, it's always you're telling me what to do. You are not allowed to talk about her.
What? Okay, let me see.
Yeah, yeah, it's like say three times. It's like Beatles use it's about to appear, you know, right?
They always usually do on my show, you know, somehow it has some like real power or something.
I don't know. Is that lucky? Yes. Yes cat. Lover shy is lucky because we've had people come on the show like
You know celebrities never sent rats snakes or pizza. Well, who has a dead snake anyway?
Nobody's killing snakes or that's just really disturbing. Let's not
Even half decent size yard or even if you don't in some areas if you live near like a water body, then yeah, you probably have snakes
Probably a lot of stuff that you don't see because they're nocturnal
the
Everyone Alice we controversial but Alice is he's a sweet guy. He's a sweet guy. I'm very sweet